<hymns> <hymn> <title>The Servant King</title> <content>From heaven you came
helpless babe Entered our world, your glory veiled Not to be served, but to
serve And give your life, that we might live

This is our God The Servant King He calls us now to follow him To bring our
lives as daily offering Of worship to the Servant King

There in the garden of tears My heavy load, he chose to bear His heart with
sorrow was torn Yet not my will but yours he said


This is our God, the Servant King He calls us now to follow him To bring our
lives as daily offering Of worship to the Servant King

Come see his hands and his feet The scars that speak of sacrifice Hands that
flung stars into space To cruel nails surrendered

This is our God, the Servant King He calls us now to follow him To bring our
lives as daily offering Of worship to the Servant King

So let us learn how to serve And in our lives enthrone him Each others needs to
prefer For it is Christ we’re serving This is our God, the Servant King

He calls us now to follow him To bring our lives as daily offering Of worship to
the Servant King </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Humble thy self in the sight of the Lord</title> <content>Humble
thy self in the sight of the Lord (Humble thy self in the sight of the
Lord)...x2

And He (And He) Shall lift (Shall lift) you up (higher and higher) And He (And
He) Shall lift (Shall lift) you up

Our God is an awesome God He reigns from heaven above With wisdom, power and
love Our God is an awesome God </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Make me a servant</title> <content>Make me a servant, humble and
meek, Lord, let me lift up those who are weak. And may the prayer of my heart
always be: Make me a servant make me a servant, Make me a servant today.

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>One God Alone</title> <content>One God Alone My God is so good One
God Alone My God is good x2 He is My Strength, my love and my song My one
desire, my hope and my rock Come taste and see My God is so good

Blessed be the one who takes refuge in Him Knowing for sure He’ll knock on your
door. Come inside Lord take over my heart. Consume me now I know you’re so good
One God Alone My God is so good One God Alone My God is good

For He has done what no other god has done. I’ll tell you what He’s shown me
real love Not like any love But one that’s so good

Love that goes above all things Lord it was you Who died for me One God Alone My
God is so good One God Alone One God above all gods

King of kings and Lord of lords My god out does them all Jesus Christ, Emmanuel
Your name above all

One God Alone My God is so good One God Alone My God is good

One God Alone My God reigns over all One Good alone My Jesus is good. </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Repentance</title> <content>A Cry of regret escapes the lips this
silent wail within, no longer bare

erupting to a thousand bits like a wild fire spreading every where

My God I call… Can you hear me? I think I’m trapped Lord pull me from the shadow
of death please save me Satan has me trapped in lethal chains now I’m bound to
sin just like a slave Please break his hold and set me free your mighty hand I
call to save

My Jesus stretch your mighty hand I’ll grab it and keep holding on I’m sinking
in sins like quick sand Just Pull me its force is way too strong My God I
call…Can you hear me? I think I’m trapped Lord pull me from the shadow of death
please save me Satan has me trapped in lethal chains now I’m bound to sin just
like a slave Please break his hold and set me free your mighty hand I call to
save

Will You please forgive me the hope is there I truly know your death on earth
sent to revive me like the thief and the paradise he knows My God I call…Can you
hear me? I think I’m trapped Lord pull me from the shadow of death please save
me Satan has me trapped in lethal chains now I’m bound to sin just like a slave
Please break his hold and set me free your mighty hand I call to save </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Lean on Him</title> <content>Sometimes in our life, we all have
pain, we all have sorrow but if we are wise, we know that there’s always
tomorrow Lean on Him, when you’re not strong And He’ll be your friend, He’ll
help you carry on For it won’t be long, ‘Til your gonna see His glory and hold
on

Please don’t waste your time He’ll have the things to heal your sorrow For no
one can feel those of your needs But Jesus alone So just call on Jesus, when you
need a hand We all need somebody to lean on You just might have a problem That
He’ll understand We all need somebody to lean on

Lean on Him, when you’re not strong And He’ll be your friend, He’ll help you
carry on For it won’t be long, ‘Til your gonna see His glory and hold on So just
call on Jesus, when you need a hand We all need somebody to lean on You just
might have a problem That He’ll understand We all need somebody to lean on

If there is a load you have to bear, That you can’t carry He’s right up the
road, He’ll share your load, If you just call Him call Him call Him call Him
call Him </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All in All</title> <content>You are my strength when I am weak
You are the treasure that I seek You are my all in all Seeking You as a precious
jewel Lord to give up, I’d be a fool You are my all in all Jesus, Lamb of God,
worthy is Your name Jesus, Lamb of God, worthy is Your name

Taking my sin, my cross, my shame Rising again, I bless Your name You are my all
in all When I fall down, You pick me up When I am dry, You fill my cup You are
my all in all Jesus, Lamb of God, worthy is Your name Jesus, Lamb of God, worthy
is Your name </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus, You’re the sweetest name of all</title> <content>Jesus,
You’re the sweetest name of all Jesus, You always hear me when I call Oh, Jesus,
You pick me up each time I fall You’re the sweetest, sweetest name of all Jesus,
You’re the son and coming King Jesus, we need the love that You can bring Oh,
Jesus, we lift our voices up and sing You’re the sweetest, sweetest name of all
Jesus, how I love to praise Your name Jesus, you’re still the first, the last,
the same Oh, Jesus, You died and took away my shame You’re the sweetest,
sweetest name of all </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Shout to the Lord</title> <content>My Jesus, my Saviour Lord there
is none like You All of my days I want to praise The wonders of Your mighty love
My comfort, my shelter Tower of refuge and strength Let every breath, all that I
am Never cease to worship You

Shout to the Lord All the Earth, let us sing Power and majesty Praise to the
King Mountains bow down And the seas will roar At the sound of Your name

I sing for joy at the work of Your hands Forever I’ll love You Forever I’ll
stand

Nothing compares To the promise I have In You </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Amazing Grace</title> <content>Amazing Grace, how sweet the sound,
That saved a wretch like me.... I once was lost, but now am found, Was blind,
but now, I see. T’was Grace that taught... my heart to fear. And Grace, my fears
relieved. How precious did that Grace appear... the hour I first believed.

Through many dangers, toils and snares... we have already come. T’was Grace that
brought us safe thus far... and Grace will lead us home. The Lord has promised
good to me... His word my hope secures. He will my shield and portion be... as
long as life endures.

Yea, when this flesh and heart shall fail, and mortal life shall cease, I shall
possess within the veil, a life of joy and peace. When we’ve been here ten
thousand years... bright shining as the sun. We’ve no less days to sing God’s
praise... then when we’ve first begun.

Amazing Grace, how sweet the sound, That saved a wretch like me.... I once was
lost but now am found, Was blind, but now, I see. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>As the deer</title> <content>As the deer pants for the water, So
my soul longs after You. You alone are my heart’s desire, And I long to worship
You.

You alone are my strength, my shield; To You alone may my spirit yield. You
alone are my heart’s desire, And I long to worship You.

You’re my friend and You are my brother Even though You are a King. I love You
more than any other, So much more than anything. You alone are my strength, my
shield; To You alone may my spirit yield. You alone are my heart’s desire, And I
long to worship You.

I want You more than gold or silver, Only You can satisfy. You alone are the
real joy giver, And on you I can rely

You alone are my strength, my shield; To You alone may my spirit yield. You
alone are my heart’s desire, And I long to worship You. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I love You, Lord</title> <content>I love You, Lord And I lift my
voice To worship You O my soul, rejoice! Take joy, My King, in what You hear,
Let it be, Let it be a sweet, sweet sound In Your ear. x2</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Give Thanks</title> <content>Give thanks with a grateful heart
Give thanks to the Holy One Give thanks because He's given Jesus Christ, His Son
x2 And now let the weak say, "I am strong" Let the poor say, "I am rich” Because
of what the Lord has done for us"x2 Give thanks Give thanks Give
thanks</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>My Search For You</title> <content>I have been a witness to your
smile, In times that have past. I believe I’ve shuddered from The protective
shadow you cast I discovered essential beauty, hid behind the mask I felt your
presence O ’Lord, for this is what I asked.

I lost you in the crowds, Lord always passing through I did without a comfort
that I once knew chose to flee the warm embrace that drew me to you I believe I
was mistaken, now what do I do?

I yearn for your guidance, I long for your light I crave your sweet silence that
carried me through the night I search now for your promise to flee this earthly
life I have one desire, that you hold me tight I lost you in the crowds, Lord
always passing through I did without a comfort that I once knew chose to flee
the warm embrace that drew me to you I believe I was mistaken, now what do I do?

I have staggered and fallen, my one goal is you I searched for the answers your
radiance shone through nothing else matters I plead for only you mourning over
failures, yet knowing you’ll renew.

I lost you in the crowds, Lord always passing through I did without a comfort
that I once knew chose to flee the warm embrace that drew me to you I believe I
was mistaken, now what do I do? </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Canticle of Creation</title> <content>As night gives birth to the
dawn and I see all the grandeur of each day. I long to have and to hold all the
wonder of your heart, all the power in your love, all the mystery embodied in
your word.

Spirit breathe your breath of love! Creation yearns for you to come. Renew your
earth, out-pour your healing care. Lord restore the harmony where human kind may
learn to see the hope, the dream in your al-mighty plan

The earth is blessed and adorned by the breath and the presence of your love.
All those who dwell in this land shall awaken to your voice. They shall stand
and give you praise and your faithfulness will be for evermore.

Spirit breathe your breath of love! Creation yearns for you to come. Renew your
earth, out-pour your healing care. Lord restore the harmony where human kind may
learn to see the hope, the dream in your al-mighty plan

As night gives birth to the dawn and I see all the grandeur of each day. I long
to have and to hold all the wonder of your heart, all the power in your love,
all the mystery embodied in your word. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Lord I Lift Your Name on High</title> <content>Lord, I lift Your
name on high; Lord, I love to sing Your praises; I’m so glad You’re in my life;
I’m so glad You came to save us. You came from Heaven to earth; To show the way,
From the earth to the cross, My debt to pay, From the cross to the grave, From
the grave to the sky; Lord, I lift Your name on high!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>You are my hiding place</title> <content>You are my hiding place
You always fill my heart With songs of deliverance Whenever I am afraid I will
trust in You I will trust in You Let the weak say I am strong In the strength of
the Lord X2</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>From all nations</title> <content>From all nations, From all
tribes, From all people From all nations, From all tribes, From all tongues
(Before the throne stand myriads, of myriads) (2x) Coming from everywhere

Coming from ailing pain, coming from a life of distain Dressed in heavenly
array, and on their strings they play They were the ones he saved with the blood
he gave) (2x) I saw them waving, as they came this way

From all nations, From all tribes, From all people From all nations, From all
tribes, From all tongues (Before the throne stand myriads, of myriads) (2x)
Coming from everywhere

Before judges they stand, in chains they’d tied their hands Injustice they bore
too, their aim so high and grand. (They were the ones he saved with the blood he
gave) (2x) I saw them thanking, as they came this way

From all nations, From all tribes, From all people From all nations, From all
tribes, From all tongues (Before the throne stand myriads, of myriads) (2x)
Coming from everywhere

In the furnace they would stroll, in prison as if at home In the spirit they
felt consoled in Christ they were absorbed (They were the ones he saved with the
blood he gave) (2x) I saw them cheering, as they came this way.

From all nations, From all tribes, From all people From all nations, From all
tribes, From all tongues (Before the throne stand myriads, of myriads) (2x)
Coming from everywhere

They were hated and Despised, their lives remained in strife their peace was not
destroyed, for praising gave them joy (They were the ones he saved with the
blood he gave) (2x) I saw them victorious as they came this way </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Above All</title> <content>Above all powers, above all kings Above
all nature and all created things Above all wisdom and all the ways of man You
were here before the world began Above all kingdoms, above all thrones Above all
wonders the world has ever known Above all wealth and treasures of the earth
There’s no way to measure what you’re worth


Crucified Laid behind a stone You lived to die Rejected and alone Like a rose
Trampled on the ground You took the fall And thought of me Above all Like a rose
Trampled on the ground You took the fall And thought of me Above all </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Seek ye</title> <content>Seek ye first the Kingdom of God And his
righteousness And all these things shall be added unto you Allelu, Allelujah
Allelujah, Allelujah, Allelujah, Allelu, Allelujah Man cannot live by bread
alone But by every word That proceeds from the mouth of God Allelu, Allelujah
Allelujah, Allelujah, Allelujah, Allelu, Allelujah

“I am the way, the truth and the life,” That’s what Jesus said. “Nobody comes to
the father but by me.” Allelu, Allelujah Allelujah, Allelujah, Allelujah,
Allelu, Allelujah Ask and it shall be given unto you Seek and ye shall find
Knock and the door shall be opened unto you Allelu, Allelujah Allelujah,
Allelujah, Allelujah, Allelu, Allelujah </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>How Deep</title> <content>How deep the Father’s love for us, How
vast beyond all measure That He should give His only Son To make a wretch His
treasure How great the pain of searing loss, The Father turns His face away As
wounds which mar the chosen One, Bring many sons to glory

Behold the Man upon a cross, My sin upon His shoulders Ashamed I hear my mocking
voice, Call out among the scoffers It was my sin that held Him there Until it
was accomplished His dying breath has brought me life I know that it is finished

I will not boast in anything No gifts, no power, no wisdom But I will boast in
Jesus Christ His death and resurrection Why should I gain from His reward? I
cannot give an answer But this I know with all my heart His wounds have paid my
ransom

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Father I adore you</title> <content>Father, I adore You Lay my
life before You How I love You Jesus, I adore You Lay my life before You How I
love You Spirit, I adore You Lay my life before You How I love You</content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>In Christ alone</title> <content></content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Mary Did You Know</title> <content></content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Shine Jesus Shine</title> <content>Lord the Light of Your Love is
shining, In the midst of the darkness shining, Jesus light of the world shine
upon us, Set us free by the truth You now bring us Shine on me. Shine on me

Shine Jesus shine...Fill this land with the Father’s glory Blaze, Spirit blaze,
Set our hearts on fire Flow, river flow Flood the nations with grace and mercy
Send forth Your word Lord and let there be light.

Lord I come to Your awesome presence, From the shadows into Your radiance, By
the blood I may enter Your brightness, Search me, try me, consume all my
darkness, Shine on me. Shine on me.

Shine Jesus shine...Fill this land with the Father’s glory Blaze, Spirit blaze,
Set our hearts on fire Flow, river flow Flood the nations with grace and mercy
Send forth Your word Lord and let there be light.

As we gaze on Your kindly brightness. So our faces display Your likeness. Ever
changing from glory to glory, Mirrored here may our lives tell Your story. Shine
on me. Shine on me.

Shine Jesus shine...Fill this land with the Father’s glory Blaze, Spirit blaze,
Set our hearts on fire Flow, river flow Flood the nations with grace and mercy
Send forth Your word Lord and let there be light. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I will enter His gates</title> <content>I will enter His gates
with thanks giving in my heart I will enter His courts with praise I will say
this is the day that the Lord has made I will rejoice for He has made me glad He
has made me glad Oh He has made me glad I will rejoice for He has made me glad
He has made me glad Oh He has made me glad I will rejoice for He has made me
glad.

I will enter His gates with thanks giving in my heart I will enter His courts
with praise I will say this is the day that the Lord has made I will rejoice for
He has made me glad He has made me glad Oh He has made me glad I will rejoice
for He has made me glad He has made me glad Oh He has made me glad I will
rejoice for He has made me glad. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I Surrender All</title> <content>All to Jesus, I surrender, All to
Him I freely give I will ever love and serve Him In His presence, daily live.

I surrender all, I surrender all, All to Thee, my blessed Saviour, I surrender
all

All to Jesus, I surrender Humbly at his feet I bow, Worldly pleasures all
forsaken Take me Jesus, take me now</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Eflogi Menos</title> <content>Blessed is He who comes in the name
of the Lord, and again in the name of the Lord Hosanna to the Son of David, and
again to the Son of David. Hosanna in the highest, and again in the highest
Hosanna to the King of Israel, and again to the King of Israel. Let us praise
saying Alleluia, Alleluia, Alleluia, Glory to our God, and again to our God

Hosanna in the Highest, this is the King of Israel, Blessed is He Who comes in,
the name of the Lord of Hosts

Truly blessed are You with Your Gracious Father and the Holy Spirit for You have
come and saved us.

That Who is sitting above the Cherubim, today appeared in Jerusalem, riding on a
colt with great glory, and multitude of angels surrounding Him.

The crowd spread garments on the road, and they cut branches from the trees,
while shouting and singing: “Hosanna to the Son of David”.

Today the sayings have been fulfilled, as said in the Prophets and proverbs, and
also Zachariah prophesied and said: a prophecy about our Lord Jesus Christ

Hosanna in the Highest, this is the King of Israel, Blessed is He Who comes in,
the name of the Lord of Hosts </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>How Lovely</title> <content>How lovely it is to get together In
love our Lord teaches us When two meet in my Name together I’ll always be in
between their gather

O Lord come now and join us here We ask You to come and give us cheer Fill us
with joy from Your Holy Spirit And peace no riches can provide

The Lord is here always with us How lovely He is, how content we are We talk to
Him and He always listens He’ll always be with us, in us

O Lord come now and join us here We ask You to come and give us cheer Fill us
with joy from Your Holy Spirit And peace no riches can provide </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>O’ Sing unto Him</title> <content>O’ Sing unto Him Who was
crucified buried and resurrected And trampled and abolished Death Praise Him and
exceedingly exalt Him. Take off the old man And put on the new one Come closer
to His great mercy Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him

Join us in praises O’ three young men Whom Christ our God has exalted And from
the Devil delivered Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him For the sake of your
God the Messiah The maker of all good things Come unto us Ananias Praise Him and
exceedingly exalt Him.

The heavens declare the glory Of God from day to day O’ you angels whom He has
made Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him. Now you powers of the Lord Bless His
honoured name O’ sun, moon, and all the stars Praise Him and exceedingly exalt
Him.

And you too rain and dew Sing praises unto our Saviour For He is the God of our
fathers Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him. Praise without apathy The Lord,
the King of kings O’ you rivers and seas Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him.

Likewise, when we look unto them Let us say with all these creatures Bless the
Lord all the birds Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him. O’ servants of the True
God And all the righteous people With all His humble beloved Praise Him and
exceedingly exalt Him.

My God is the One Who saved you from all danger O’ Sedrak, Mesak, and Abednego
Praise Him and exceedingly exalt Him. Hurry and be very vigilant O’ you
righteous of the Lord And all the creatures whom He has made Praise Him and
exceedingly exalt Him.

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Holy are You</title> <content>Holy are You O’ Lord and King Maker
of heaven and earth, With Jesus Christ the life giver, And the Holy Spirit.
Righteous is the Son, the Lamb of God, And praised by the heavenly hosts With
His glorious Father, And the Holy Spirit Helper and giver of life, the Spirit of
God, Spirit of Truth, the Comforter. One Trinity the Father, and the Son, And
the Holy Spirit.

Honoured and exalted is the Father, From all the tribes and all the tongues, And
praised with Jesus Christ His son, And the Holy Spirit. Compassionate is the
Word of God The Good Shepherd, who was crucified for our sins, And saved us from
our death, With the Holy Spirit. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Prince Of Peace</title> <content>Prince of peace is risen He is
risen indeed Alleluia, Alleluia The Lord is risen At dawn of Sunday Mary
Magdalene had gone With some spices and ointments For the Beloved One But Lord
Jesus is risen Triumphantly at dawn And the angel of the Lord Rolled over the
stone

Mary wept when she saw The tomb was empty And asked “Sir, Where have you taken
the body?” Then Lord Jesus said to Mary “I am He” “I have risen, Go and tell
everybody”

To the gathered disciples Mary had gone Preaching “Lord Jesus is risen, He lives
on” Then Jesus came and showed them His hands and side And so the joy In hearts
did abide

Alleluia, The good news is verified Alleluia, He’s risen and glorified Alleluia,
To the Saviour of all men Alleluia, The thorn of death is broken Prince of peace
is risen He is risen indeed Alleluia, Alleluia The Lord is risen </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Light of the world</title> <content>Light of the World, You
stepped down into darkness. Opened my eyes let me see. Beauty that makes this
heart adore You. Hope of a life spent with You. So here I am to worship, Here I
am to bow down. Here I am to say that You’re my God. You’re altogether lovely,
altogether worthy. Altogether wonderful to me.

King of all days, Oh so highly exalted. Glorious in Heaven above. Humbly You
came to the earth You created. All for love’s sake became poor. So here I am to
worship, Here I am to bow down. Here I am to say that You’re my God. You’re
altogether lovely, altogether worthy. Altogether wonderful to me. I’ll never
know how much it cost To see my sins up on that cross......x3 </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Sing Alleluia</title> <content>My Lord He died for a kingdom To
redeem the hearts of men Now my people don’t you weep He has risen from His
sleep He lives again, Alleluia

Sing Alleluia, the Lord is Risen He has Risen indeed Alleluia

My Lord came forth like the morning With the splender of the sun Came triumphant
from the womb From the darkness of the tomb The victory won, Alleluia

Sing Alleluia, the Lord is Risen He has Risen indeed Alleluia

My Lord united our mountains With the everlasting hills Now the seasons and the
sea Sing the son of victory Rock and rills, Alleluia

Sing Alleluia, the Lord is Risen He has Risen indeed Alleluia


My Lord renewed all creation That had waited late and long Now we all with one
accord Live and love the risen Lord This is our song, Alleluia

Sing Alleluia, the Lord is Risen He has Risen indeed Alleluia

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Father God</title> <content>Father God I wonder how I managed to
exist Without the knowledge of Your Fatherhood And Your loving Care But now I am
Your child, I am adopted in Your family And I will never be alone ‘Cause Father
God You’re there beside me I will sing Your praises, I will sing Your praise I
will Sing Your praise, Forever more! (x2) </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>The Eve of the Last Supper</title> <content>1)The eve of the last
supper, the eve of the last supper, He took bread and broke it, and said this is
My body (2) Chorus Our Saviour gave to us the wine of His love, Saved us revived
us Jesus the love of my heart, Jesus the love of my heart (X 2) 2) The eve of my
Lord’s sufferings, The eve of my Lord’s sufferings, He took the Chalice and gave
thanks, and said this is My blood, (2) 3) My heart I give to You, and my
possessions are Yours, strengthen my hope in You, O’ You the fountain of love,
(2) 4) They took You to the garden, and wrapped You in the shroud, O’ You the
Gardener, where did they lay my Lord?(2) 5)He arose from the dead, surprising
everyone, and the angel proclaimed, to Jesus the love of my heart, (2).

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Golgotha</title> <content>Golgotha in Hebrew Calvary in Greek The
place where You Were crucified O’ Lord You stretched Your hands And they
Crucified Two thieves with You, On Your right and on Your left And You in the
midst O’ Good Saviour Glory be to the Father, the Son And the Holy Spirit

The right thief, Cried saying: “Remember me my Lord Remember me my Saviour
Remember me my King When You come in Your Kingdom” The Lord answered him, in a
humble voice ‘Today you will be with Me in My Kingdom’ Now and forevermore Amen.
The righteous Joseph and Nicodemus Came and took Christ’s body And placed Him in
a tomb

They praised Him saying: “Holy God, Holy Almighty, Holy Immortal, Who was
crucified for us Have mercy on us” Glory be to the Father The Son and the Holy
Spirit Now and forevermore Amen. We also worship Him Crying and saying “Have
mercy on us O’ God our Saviour Who was crucified on the cross And crushed Satan
under our feet” </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Come Let Us Worship</title> <content>(Come let us worship and bow
down Let us kneel before the Lord, Our God, our Maker For He is our God And we
are the people of His pasture And the sheep of His hand Just the sheep of His
hand) x2 </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Agnus Dei</title> <content>Alle-lu-ia Alle-lu-ia For our Lord God
Almighty Reigns Alle-lu-ia Alle-lu-ia For our Lord God Almighty Reigns
Alle-lu-ia

Ho-o-ly, Holy Are You Lord God Almighty Worthy is the Lamb Worthy is the Lamb
You are Holy, Holy Are You Lord God Almighty Worthy is the Lamb Worthy is the
Lamb You are Holy </content> </hymn>


<hymn> <title>Rock of My Salvation</title> <content>You are the rock of my
salvation You are the strength of my life You are my hope and my inspiration
Lord unto You will I cry I believe in You, believe in You For Your faithful love
to me You have been my help in time of need....... Lord unto You will I plead
</content> </hymn>


<hymn> <title>Very early Sunday morning</title> <content>Very early Sunday
morning While the guards were still asleep Our Lord arose declaring His promise
He did keep. Chorus Resurrection is my song Resurrection gave me life
Resurrection made me strong Jesus my Lord is alive. Jesus is risen in glory
Heaven and earth sang and praised And the angel told the story He is risen as He
said. Mary Magdalene was looking In the garden for her Lord Jesus Himself was
telling Her to go and spread the word. All the disciples were praying They were
truly in great fear When Mary came to them saying He is risen, He is not here.
While they were in the room Jesus Christ Himself appeared My peace I give to you
And My peace with you I leave

But Thomas did not believe What the disciples had seen So Jesus again appeared
Showed him the place of the spear. Tell the Marys to cease mourning Among the
dead do not seek For Jesus our Lord is living Giving power to the weak. Jesus my
victorious Lord Conquered the powers of Hades And the thorn of death He broke My
salvation He proclaims. The heavenly hosts were singing Welcoming our glorious
Lord Heavens joy was overwhelming Jesus opened its doors Alleluia, Alleluia
Risen is the King of peace Alleluia, Alleluia Truly He’s risen indeed Chorus
Resurrection is my song Resurrection gave me life Resurrection made me strong
Jesus my Lord is alive. Jesus is risen in glory Heaven and earth sang and
praised And the angel told the story He is risen as He said. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>The Baker Woman</title> <content></content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>We worship (The Prime Doxology)</title> <content>We worship the
Father, the SonAnd the Holy Spirit Hail to the church The house of the angels
Hail to the Virgin Who brought forth our Saviour Hail to Gabriel Who brought her
the good news Hail to Michael The Archangel Hail to the Twenty four priests Hail
to the Cherubim Hail to the Seraphim Hail to all The heavenly orders

Hail to St John The great fore-runner Hail to the Twelve apostles Hail to our
father Mark the Evangelist The destroyer Of the idols Hail to Stephen The first
martyr Hail to George The morning star Hail to all the choirs Of the martyrs
Hail to Abba Antony And the three Macarii Hail to all the choirs Of the cross
bearers Hail to all the saints Who have pleased the Lord Through their prayers O
Christ our King Accord to us mercy In Thy kingdom </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Seven Times</title> <content>Seven times each day With all my
heart I bless Your name O’ Lord of all. I remembered Your Name And was comforted
O’ King of kings And God of gods. Jesus Christ Our true God Who was incarnated
For our salvation. Of the Holy Spirit, And of Saint Mary The pure Bride. And
turned our sorrow And all our anguish Into heartily joy And complete rejoicing.
Let us kneel unto Him And chant To His mother Mary The beautiful dove.

And shout with rejoicing voices saying: Sherene Maria, mother of Emmanuel.
Sherene Maria, rescue of Adam our father Sherene Maria, mother of our refuge
Sherene Maria, cheers of Eve Sherene Maria, joy of generations Sherene Maria,
joy of the righteous Abel Sherene Maria, true Virgin Sherene Maria, rescue of
Noah Sherene Maria, innocent peaceful lady Sherene Maria, beauty of Abraham
Sherene Maria, O’ great crown Sherene Maria, rescue of Isaac the saint
</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Sherene Maria</title> <content>Sherene Maria, mother of the Holy
Sherene Maria, cheer of Jacob Sherene Maria, joy of the multitudes Sherene
Maria, honour of Judah Sherene Maria, mother of the Lord Sherene Maria, strength
of the righteous job Sherene Maria, O’ precious stone Sherene Maria, mother of
the Beloved Sherene Maria, daughter of David Sherene Maria, patron of Solomon
Sherene Maria, help of the righteous Sherene Maria, rescue of Isaiah Sherene
Maria, healing of Jeremiah Sherene Maria, knowledge of Ezekiel Sherene Maria,
favour of Daniel Sherene Maria, strength of Elijah Sherene Maria, beauty of
Elisha Sherene Maria, mother of God Sherene Maria, mother of Jesus Christ
Sherene Maria, beautiful dove Sherene Maria, mother of God’s Son </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>St Mark?</title> <content>Honoured are you Oh St Mark. The pure
disciple and evangelist In your house they held the first Eucharist Your home
became our first church Blessed is your upper room Oh St Mark Where Lord Jesus
gave His covenant He washed and filled the disciples With the Holy spirit
Beholder of God, this is yor name One of the seventy Apostles Selected as
Christ’s disciple You went to preach the Gospel Many were your miracles with the
power of God Your father believed when you shouted OH CHRIST THE SON OF GOD SAVE
US And the lions perished Destroyer of idols You served cities Guided by the
Holy Spirit You found your way to Egypt After preaching in Libya You came to
Alexandria with a torn sandal Faced all the religions and philosophies By the
power of Cod you defeated them With your prayers and pleadings Ananias the
cobbler not knowing Christ Mending your sandals. pierced his thumb To your
delight he screamed saying EIS THEOS. OH THE ONE GOD Blessed are you Ananias
with an open heart Saint Mark taught you about Christ baptized you and you were
made a bishop And the faith spread throughout the land

blessed are you Oh Saint Mark you changed the land Which was full of darkness
and sin To a heavenly paradise With justice shining over it The flourish of
goodness throughout the land Caused the devil to conduct a scheme By stirring
the Romans and Pagans to rise and slay you was their plan With a rope around
your neck you were captured And like Jesus you were tortured You thanked the
Lord for being worthy And the angel appeared saying: Oh Mark the good servant,
the time has come To receive your award Be courageous as your name has been
Written in the book of life Jesus said to him OH MARK MY DESCIPLE AND MY
EVANGELIST PEACE BE WITH YOU Mark screamed and said MY LORD JESUS Blessed are
you Oh St Mark the crown holder Who taught the Copts about our Lord Oh
honourable intercessor And GLORY BE TO GOD </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>My Coptic Church</title> <content>My Coptic Church. The church of
the Lord Ancient and Strong, I wish her long life In the early years, After the
birth of Christ St. Mark came bearing, The light of the true faith He dwelt in
the land, proclaiming salvation In the name of our Redeemer, Christ who removed
our sins

The Copts then believed, in the Lord Jesus And Joy filled all the cities of
Egypt In a very very short time, He abolished all idols The cross was exalted,
the sign of the faith Satan quickly rose, to war the Son of God He stirred the
rulers, emperors and armies He then declared war, on the sons of the faith Deny
your Christ, or be thrown in the fire Our honored fathers, elders and youngsters
Were not moved by pain, distress nor dishonor But said courageously, forward no
turning back We don’t fear fire, Our Lord is Jesus Christ

They were beaten and imprisoned, they lived in oppression They were burned and
killed, and tasted every pain By the power of their faith, they overcame their
pains And remained believing in, the King of Peace With blood and suffering,
they bought the faith And preserved it for us, in the name of Our Savior

Let us all rise, from our laziness With diligence seeking, the heavenly rewards
The Church of the Fathers, you are our pride To her success, let us all join
together My Coptic Church, her faith is orthodox Forever strong, Egypt is
Christ’s </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>St Mark</title> <content>I’ll tell you a tale of one who you’ll
see One of the greatest you’ll ever meet He’s a rock he’s a rod The beholder of
God And He came out to preach Salvation for humanity

St Mark, you came, you spoke, you served a world… Where Idols flourished…them
every man had worshipped St Mark you died, could not deny, for One…. Who brought
salvation to every single nation

In his life, he came to know many trials But more than that it had all wonders
and smiles Like when he served and poured… out water and saw A miraculous flow,
of wine pour out amazingly

St Mark, you came, you spoke, you served a world… Where Idols flourished…them
every man had worshipped St Mark you died, could not deny, for One…. Who brought
salvation to every single nation In his

In his dwelling stayed the One we adore To his disciples he came just before He
would give them the love, Of the Father above And the Spirit who will preach
This message of His love for all

St Mark, you came, you spoke, you served a world… Where Idols flourished…them
every man had worshipped St Mark you died, could not deny, for One…. Who brought
salvation to every single nation

Those were the days we can look to see Him Who led you to your long journey In
Egypt you have served And The people have heard They loved you fervently, Those
people are our families </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Saint Mark’s Doxology</title> <content>Hail to you Saint Mark The
son of Arostopolos Who preached the name of Isos Markos Piapostolos. You were
born in Cyrene And fled to Palestine The land of the Divine Markos Piapostolos.
You followed Jesus Christ From the east to the west While He was in your midst
Markos Piapostolos.

When the lions attacked You and your father prayed So immediately they died
Markos Piapostolos. Our Lord sent Peter To prepare the Passover In the house of
your father Markos Piapostolos. You were carrying a pitcher that was full of
water They followed till you entered Markos Piapostolos.

And the Lord said This is My body and blood For you it is shed Markos
Piapostolos. To the garden you followed The men of you laid hold You fled from
them naked Markos Piapostolos. In your house the Comforter Descended like fire
God answered your prayer Markos Piapostolos.

With tongues you spoke to men From every nation About the resurrection Markos
Piapostolos. You brought us the good news About Piekhrestos And ordained Anianos
Markos Piapostolos. You wrote the first witness About Jesus’ greatness
Describing His Holiness Markos Piapostolos.

In Alexandria you built A school that was the first Many Popes graduated from it
Markos Piapostolos. And when you were martyred Your body was not burned God
ordered and it rained Markos Piapostolos. You are God’s beholder And our
intercessor Remember us in your prayer Markos Piapostolos. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Awesome God</title> <content>Our God is an awesome God He reigns
from heaven above With wisdom, power and love Our God is an awesome God Our God
is an awesome God He reigns from heaven above With wisdom, power and love Our
God is an awesome God </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>One in you</title> <content>There is one Man who lived for us One
Man who died for us, that’s You You came to reconcile us One Man who unites us,
that’s You

Together we stand as one at the cross We lift our hands to You Jesus We love You
Jesus We worship Jesus We’re one in You x2

We’re one in You We lift Your name We give You praise We’re one in You x2
</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Perfect Servant</title> <content>Jesus, You are Jesus, You were
Jesus, You will always be A perfect Servant to us A perfect Servant to death
Even death on a cross Give us a picture of Your face Show us the measure of Your
grace Reveal the love of the Father Put within us tenderness Release from us all
selfishness We’ll consider them better We are Yours Give us hearts of servants
</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Lord i give you my heart</title> <content>This is my desire – to
honour You Lord with all my heart I worship You All I have within me I give You
praise All that I adore is in You Lord I give You my heartt I give You my soul I
live for You alone Every breath that I take Every moment I’m awake Lord have
Your way in me </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Ekhristos Anesti</title> <content>Ekhristos Anesti Alithos Anesti
Christ has risen! He has truly risen! {Jesus the compassionate was crucified to}
x2 redeem the human race from the fortress of Satan

Ekhristos Anesti Alithos Anesti Christ has risen! He has truly risen! {After
three days while it was dark} x2 And the people were sleeping Christ has risen!

Ekhristos Anesti Alithos Anesti Christ has risen! He has truly risen! The
disciples were afraid and the soldiers were standing} x2 And the Marys were
going they found that Christ has risen

Ekhristos Anesti Alithos Anesti Christ has risen! He has truly risen! Oh,
disciples of Jesus Oh, all you crowds} x2 Wipe away the tears Christ has risen

Ekhristos Anesti Alithos Anesti Christ has risen! He has truly risen! {How
beautiful, is the feast of the glorious Resurrection} x2 And every Sunday a
feast Christ has risen

Ekhristos Anesti Alithos Anesti Christ has risen He has truly risen Ekhristos
Anesti Alithos Anesti Christ has risen He has truly risen </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Hold my hand and lead</title> <content>My soul is crushed and my
heart is faint Please hear the voice of my complaint (Yet I shall wait only for
the Lord) x2 (He fills my heart with glorious joy) x2 Chorus Out of the depth
have I cried to Thee O’ Lord, hear me and have mercy (Why don’t You hold my hand
and lead) x2 (Because I am really in great need) x2

Here I am surrounded by the sea The water round me is too deep (And I am about
to drown in my sins) x2 (You are my refuge, please set me free) x2 Chorus Out of
the depth have I cried to Thee O’ Lord, hear me and have mercy (Why don’t You
hold my hand and lead) x2 (Because I am really in great need) x2

Jonah had prayed from the depth of the whale For with the Lord no body shall
fail (Out of the valley of death he cried) x2 (‘cause Jonah had great hope in
God) x2 Chorus Out of the depth have I cried to Thee O’ Lord, hear me and have
mercy (Why don’t You hold my hand and lead) x2 (Because I am really in great
need) x2

Pour out your heart before the Lord Repent and sing a praise to His Name (Trust
in Him and you will be saved) x2 (And you will live in the house of God) x2
Chorus Out of the depth have I cried to Thee O’ Lord, hear me and have mercy
(Why don’t You hold my hand and lead) x2 (Because I am really in great need) x2

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>How great thou art</title> <content>O Lord My Lord, when I in
awesome wonder Consider all, the worlds they hands have made I see the stars, I
hear the rolling thunder Thy power throughout the universe displayed! Then sings
my soul my saviour God to thee, how great thou art how great thou art Then sings
my soul my saviour God to thee, how great thou art how great thou art

When through the woods and forest glades I wonder and hear the birds sing
sweetly in the trees. when I look down from lofty mountains grandeur and hear
the brook and feel the gentle breeze Then sings my soul my saviour God to thee,
how great thou art how great thou art Then sings my soul my saviour God to thee,
how great thou art how great thou art

And when I think that God His Son not sparing Sent Him to die, I scarce can take
it in That on the cross, my burden gladly bearing He bled and died to take away
my sin Then sings my soul my saviour God to thee, how great thou art how great
thou art Then sings my soul my saviour God to thee, how great thou art how great
thou art

When Christ Shall come with shouts of acclimation and take me home, what joy
shall fill my heart then I shall bow in humble adoration and there proclaim my
God How great thou art Then sings my soul my saviour God to thee, how great thou
art how great thou art Then sings my soul my saviour God to thee, how great thou
art how great thou art </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Come Sing A Song Of Joy</title> <content>Come sing a song of joy
For peace has come my brother Sing, sing a song of joy And let us love each
other One man shall open the door By showing love more than we know No man can
stand alone With outstretched hands before him Reach out and take them in yours
With love that endures forevermore Then sing a song of joy For love and
understanding Come sing a song of joy For we are freed my brother Sing, sing a
song of joy And let us love each other One mighty voice will acclaim That love
is the aim of every heart Then sing a song of joy For love has come among us

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Thy Word</title> <content>Chorus (Thy Word is a lamp unto my feet
And a light unto my path) 2 When I feel afraid and think I’ve lost my way Still
You’re there right beside me Nothing will I fear as long as You are near Please
be near me to the end Chorus (Thy Word is a lamp unto my feet And a light unto
my path) 2

I will not forget Your love for me and yet My heart forever is wondering Jesus
be my guide and hold me to Your side And I will love You to the end Chorus (Thy
Word is a lamp unto my feet And a light unto my path) You’re the Light unto my
path </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Spirit of Truth</title> <content>Let us praise the Lord For He is
glorified by glory Chorus He ascended to the highest heaven And sent to us the
Paraclete Spirit of truth the comforter Amen. Alleluia

Come all you nations In order to worship Jesus Christ Chorus He ascended to the
highest heaven And sent to us the Paraclete Spirit of truth the comforter Amen.
Alleluia

This is our God our Saviour And the Lord of everybody Chorus He ascended to the
highest heaven And sent to us the Paraclete Spirit of truth the comforter Amen.
Alleluia

Complete Triune, three in One The Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit Spirit of
truth the comforter Amen. Alleluia Chorus He ascended to the highest heaven And
sent to us the Paraclete Spirit of truth the comforter Amen. Alleluia </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>In the Darkness</title> <content>In the Darkness all alone Tears
rolling down my face I say Father, Father And I still can’t hear anything Lord I
do not fit in Lord they don’t understand What is my reason for living? What
purpose do you have planned?

Oh Lord have you abandoned me? Where are you in my time of need? I seek an
answer and I still feel alone And now I don’t know which way to flee

Father, God how could I doubt It was I who turned and left It’s all very clear
now I was in Your hands In your time I know It will all be fine And if I’m still
weary Remind me your plan is divine

I wait for the day when I will be among the saints coming to see Your glory,
your peace and Your loving care No worry no pain for eternity </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Beautiful beyond description</title> <content>You are beautiful
beyond description More wonderful than any eye can see You alone deserve my deep
devotion And to You alone, I bow on bended knee

Victorious in battle, You have rescued me So with all my heart, I lift my voice
and sing You are beautiful beyond description And forever I will worship You as
King </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Author of Beauty</title> <content>The heavens are blue,
proclaiming to You The glory of God their creator At sunset or night they’re a
beautiful sight Yes they show forth the glory of God

Author of beauty, God on high It is for You that I sigh As long as I live my
love I shall give To You, Lord my God, most high And all my days I will sing to
Your praise I adore You my God, most high The surging of seas, the wind in the
trees Breathe a music of God in nature In songs of a bird nature’s music is
heard Yes they sing forth the glory of God </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Here I Am Lord</title> <content>I the Lord of sea and sky I have
heard My people cry All who dwell in dark and sin My hand will save I who made
the stars of the night I will make their darkness bright Who will bear My light
to them? Whom shall I send? Chorus Here I am Lord, is it I Lord? I have heard
You calling in the night I will go Lord, if You lead me I will hold Your people
in my heart I the Lord of snow and rain I have born My people’s pain I have wept
for love of them They turn away I will break their hearts of stone Give them
hearts for love alone Who will speak My word to them? Whom shall I send? I the
Lord of wind and flame I will tend the poor and lame I will set a feast for them
My hand will save Finest bread I will provide Till their hearts be satisfied I
will give My life to them Whom shall I send? </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I Sing Praises To Your Name</title> <content>(I sing praises to
Your Name, O’ Lord Prises to Your Name, O’ Lord, For Your Name is great And
greatly to be praised) 2 (I give glory to Your Name, O’ Lord Glory to Your Name,
O’ Lord, For Your Name is great And greatly to be praised) </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I’ve Got The Joy, Joy, Joy</title> <content>I’ve got the joy, joy,
joy, joy Down in my heart, where? Down in my heart, where? Down in my heart.
I’ve got the joy, joy, joy, joy Down in my heart, where? Down in my heart to
stay Chorus And I’m so happy So very happy I’ve got the love of Jesus in my
heart Yes, I am so happy, so very happy I’ve got the love of Jesus in my heart
I’ve got a love for all people Down in my heart, where? Down in my heart, where?
Down in my heart. I’ve got a love for all people Down in my heart, where? Down
in my heart to stay </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus Lover Of My Soul</title> <content>Jesus, lover of my soul
Jesus, I will never let You go; You’ve taken me from the miry clay, You’ve set
my feet upon a rock and now I know I love You, I need You, Though my world
should fall, I’ll never let You go. My Saviour, my closest friend, I will
worship You until the very end. x2 </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus Is Alive In Me</title> <content>I’ll sing a song with sounds
of joy To glorify Your Name Glory and honour to You My Saviour and my Lord For
You are my God who lives Forever in my heart I’ll sing a song with sounds of joy
Jesus is alive in me Chorus Jesus is alive in me Jesus is alive in me This is
the song of victory Jesus is alive in me And even if I am sad one day And
troubles come my way My confidence is in the Lord Who is at work in me I lift my
heart and pray to Him Knowing that He will hear My strength’s ever renewed
because Jesus is alive in me The living One is sure at work Forever in my heart
And since You are alive my Lord How can I ever die Many thanks to You my source
of life For Your abundant love My banner high above me says Jesus is alive in me

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>This Is The Day</title> <content>This is the day, this is the day
That the Lord has made That the Lord has made We will rejoice, we will rejoice
And be glad in it And be glad in it This is the day that the Lord has made We
will rejoice, and be glad in it This is the day, this is the day That the Lord
has made </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>When I Look Into Your Holiness</title> <content>When I look into
Your Holiness When I gaze into Your Loveliness When all things that surround
become shadows In the light of You Chorus (I worship You, I worship You The
reason I live, is to worship You) 2 When I’ve found the joy of reaching Your
heart When my will becomes enthralled in Your love When all things that surround
become shadows In the light of You </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Just Like The Bird</title> <content>Chorus Just like the bird when
it found it’s home Just like a happy dove Your house O’ Lord, I love Your house
I love with honesty Your house is prayer, praise and candles Your house is love,
light and peace Just as I love Your house O’ Lord I love You unto the end of day
Your house is full of blessings Protected against all demons We celebrate there
the liturgies They’re prayed for all the saints In Your house we read the Bible
And learn there the nicest songs And hear there the blessed hymns And praise You
all our lives Blessed are they who are blameless O’ Lord in Your house living
Confirm me in Your luminous ways Forever and ever, Amen. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>King of Kings</title> <content>(King of kings and Lord of lords
Glory, Hallelujah) 2 (Jesus Prince of peace Glory, Hallelujah) 2 Repeat

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>When The Spirit Of The Lord</title> <content>(When the Spirit of
the Lord moves in my heart I will love as Jesus loves) 2 (I will love, I will
love I will love as Jesus loves) 2 (When the Spirit of the Lord moves in my
heart I will pray as David prayed) 2 (I will pray, I will pray I will pray as
David prayed) 2 (When the Spirit of the Lord moves in my heart I will preach as
Peter preached) 2 (I will preach, I will preach I will preach I will preach) 2
(When the Spirit of the Lord moves in my heart, I will serve as St. Paul served)
2 (I will serve, I will serve, I will serve as St. Paul served)2 </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Change My Heart O’ God</title> <content>(Change my heart O’ God
Make it ever true Change my heart O’ God May I be like You) 2 You are the potter
I am the clay Mould me and make me This is what I pray Change my heart O’ God
Make it ever true Change my heart O’ God May I be like You </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Don’t Leave Me Alone</title> <content>No don’t leave me alone O my
faithful Shepherd Guide me dear Master And be unto me a Helper Chorus (I am O
Lord without You nothing at all) 2 (So take my right hand, O Lord and guide me
In Your way forever) 2 And don’t leave me alone In the midst of this darkness
Let Your bright face guide me O Lord unto peace And don’t leave me alone But
hear my prayers And be there for me dear Lord For the rest of my life And don’t
leave me alone Because of my great sins But forgive me O Lord And accept my
repentance No don’t leave me alone In this dark empty world I’m longing for You
Lord To take me to Your rest </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Agios isteen</title> <content>O Kirios metaso. Agios istin:
opateer vasilevsin: the penthevio: genos enzoxin: tou epnevma to agio. Zee-keos
istin: opateer eovoeethin: the-penthevio: zoeen en-eporanion: tou epnevma to
agio. Ee-panos istin: opateer thi-savrin: the-penthevio: Ieesos en-eporanion: to
epnevma tou agio. Kee-rios istin: opateer lalevsin: thepenthevio: matos
en-eporanion: to epnevma tou agio. Nee-mios istin: opateer exalevsin:
the-penthevio: ondos en-eporanion: to epnevma to agio. Pee-menos istin: opateer
raravsin: the-penthevio: stavros en-eporanion: to epnevma to agio. Tee-mios
istin: opateer eemonfin: the-penthevio: fosteer en-eporanion: to epnevma to
agio. Shere istin istin: opateer epsalevsin: the-penthevio: ondos eneporanion:
to epnevma to agio. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I Place My Soul</title> <content>I Place My Soul Into Your Hand I
place my soul into Your hands My Lord Jesus Christ. Lead me ‘cause I depend on
You, Lead me and I’ll serve You Please be my guide in every way Be my guard I
won’t go astray Sanctify my heart and my needs Until I see You Lord. Chorus (As
You have always said O’ source of all goodness) 2 Come unto Me all you weary
Come unto Me and you will find rest Come unto Me I am the Way I am the Truth and
Life

When my life gets filled with worries And darkness overwhelms The clouds will be
dispersed away By You O’ Prince of Peace. You are my shield, You are my hope You
are my strength, You are my goal You are the perfect love, O’ Lord Of whom then
shall I fear? Chorus (As You have always said O’ source of all goodness) 2 Come
unto Me all you weary Come unto Me and you will find rest Come unto Me I am the
Way I am the Truth and Life

You are my Shepherd I’ll not want Lead me to still waters Restore my soul, I’m
calling You, Lead me to righteousness Though I walk through the death valley
With You I will fear no evil You are my comfort, staff and rod All the days of
my life. Chorus (As You have always said O’ source of all goodness) 2 Come unto
Me all you weary Come unto Me and you will find rest Come unto Me I am the Way I
am the Truth and Life

Come take your cross and follow Me Fear not I am with thee. Cheer up I’ve
overcome the world Your tears I’ll wipe away I showed you My love on the cross
And if you’re faithful unto death I will give you eternal life Come now and
follow Me Chorus (As You have always said O’ source of all goodness) 2 Come unto
Me all you weary Come unto Me and you will find rest Come unto Me I am the Way I
am the Truth and Life </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>O Mother of the human race</title> <content>O Mother of the human
race We Honour you O full of grace Queen of Heaven, beautiful dove Fountain of
unending love We ask of you to pray for us To God your son who dwells above To
help us in all our trials And keep us safe O Theotokos

Chosen by God our Father, For your purity and love to Him Gabriel brough you
Good news And now all nations call you blessed We ask of you to pray for us To
God your son who dwells above To help us in all our trials And keep us safe O
Theotokos

Your Son the only begotten, was condemned to the death of the Cross They
tortured and spat on him, Your Heart was Torn O Parthenos We ask of you to pray
for us To God your son who dwells above To help us in all our trials And keep us
safe O Theotokos

O blessed rod of Aaron, Who appeared to St. Thomas And Stood on the Domes of the
church Please come and visit us. And Teach us how to worship Him, And fill us
with His Holy Grace, That we may look unto you to see our blessed saviour come
We ask of you to pray for us To God your son who dwells above To help us in all
our trials And keep us safe O Theotokos </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Power of Your Love</title> <content>Lord I come to you, Let my
heart be changed, renewed Flowing from the grace that I’ve found in You. And
Lord I’ve come to know, The weaknesses I see, in me Will be stripped away, By
the power of Your love Hold me close, let your love surround me Bring me near,
draw me to your side And as I wait, I’ll rise up like the eagle And I will soar
with You, Your spirit leads me on In the power of Your love. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Who am I</title> <content>Who am I to be part of Your people The
ones that are called by Your Name Could I be chosen as one of Your own? Could it
be that our blood is the same? How can a stranger, a remnant of nations Belong
to the Royal line? You showed Your grace When the branches were broken And I was
grafted into the vine Chorus (Blessed be the Name of the Lord) 4 How could You
show me such bountiful mercy By taking the life of the Lamb? Your love is grater
than I can imagin I love You with all that I am Praise to You Jesus, the veil
has been parted And what was once secret is known Now I can cry to You Father my
Father And praise You as one of Your Own </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>At the Cross</title> <content>Oh Lord You’ve Searched me You know
my way even when I fail you I know you love me Your Holy presence Surrounding me
in every season I know You Love, I know You Love

At the Cross I bow my knee where your blood was shed for me there’s no greater
Love than this... You have overcome the grave Glory fills the highest place what
can seperate me now </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Hungry</title> <content>Hungry, I come to you For I know you
satisfy I am empty but I know Your love does not run dry So I wait for You So I
wait for You I’m falling on my knees Offering all of me Jesus, You’re all this
heart is living for Broken, I run to You For Your arms are open wide I am weary,
but I know Your touch restores my life So I wait for You So I wait for You
</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Open The Eyes of My Heart</title> <content>(Open the eyes of my
heart Lord Open the eyes of my heart I want to see You I want to see You) x2 To
see You high and lifted up Shining in the light of Your glory Pour out Your
power and love As we sing holy, holy, holy You are.................Holy Holy
Holy We Sing.................Holy Holy Holy You are.................Holy Holy
Holy I want to see you

(Open the eyes of my heart Lord Open the eyes of my heart I want to see You I
want to see You) x2 To see You high and lifted up Shining in the light of Your
glory Pour out Your power and love As we sing holy, holy, holy You
are.................Holy Holy Holy We Sing.................Holy Holy Holy You
are.................Holy Holy Holy I want see you </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Find Me</title> <content>I’m lost in the wilderness A state I’ve
carved from own I’ve hidden my existence Not knowing where I belong Chorus We
cry, We mourn, We beg for Your mercy, They laugh, They scorn, They teach the
world hypocrisy

Lands and fields surround me I walk before I run Lord be quick to find me The
end has now begun Chorus We cry, We mourn, We beg for Your mercy, They laugh,
They scorn, They teach the world hypocrisy.

We stand fast in Your Holy Law Feeling safe wherever we’re led Sure of Your love
and grave As You’re our Daily Bread Chorus We cry, We mourn, We beg for Your
mercy, They laugh, They scorn, They teach the world hypocrisy.

I hear war, I see violence, Spreading across the seas The masterpiece created
Begs for it all to cease Chorus We cry, We mourn, We beg for Your mercy, They
laugh, They scorn, They teach the world hypocrisy. I pray, For love to abound
For faith to be found For grace to surround </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Give thanks</title> <content>Give Thanks to the LORD! Call upon
His Name Make known His deeds among you Sing unto Him Sing Psalms to Him Talk of
all His wondrous works Glory in Your Name! We shout out loud and say Let the
hearts rejoice Who lift their voice And seek His Holy face! x 2

Go seek the LORD! and all His strength His works never forget how marvelous are
all things which He has done to me Glory in Your Name! We shout out loud and say
Let the hearts rejoice who lift their voice and seek His Holy face! x 2
</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Shephard of my soul</title> <content>O Thou in whose presence
delighteth my soul And whom in my distress I call My comfort by day and my
refuge by night My stronghold whenever I fall. Shepherd of my soul I beg Thee to
tell Where thou keepest thy sheep to rest For why should I roam in the valley of
tears And wander as one who is lost. I ask thee to tell me daughters of Zion
Have ye seen the One I adore I seek him in vain in the night of my soul But lo!
I can find Him no more.

Shepherd of my soul I shall follow Thee O how sweet Thy voice is to me So guide
me and lead me and show me the way My only desire is Thee. I am my beloved’s and
He is mine too He calleth me sister and spouse O how do I long for the day we
shall wed In heaven in His Father’s house.

Because the Lord is Good I will lift His Name HIGHER Everywhere I go I will lift
His Name x2 </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Each time I sin</title> <content>I know that it’s not You my Lord
who’s left me But my own blackened sin has dimed my path I stumble I am lost and
I am falling And then I see you cry out for my soul I’m about to pierce Your
side with sinful soldiers Then I crumble at Your feet ..it’s me You’ve saved!
Though I wound and scar and dig for you a grave Lord You stand knocking at my
door Till I return just like before

And each time I sin I know that I am spearing you I know sin is what the tears
that wet your cheeks But still I stop and trample out your sweetness All to
taste the bitterness of sin in your defeat Now I’m knocking at Your door Lord do
you hear me? Is it too late for my heart to come to You I am hungry and I’m
thirsty for Your Love Lord I’m weak and now Your sweetness my soul yearns

Will You leave my spirit mourning and lonely? Or will You hear my cry and spare
me from my fate? You said Dear Lord you’d never leave a sinner My sin is the
reason that You came I see clearly now how deeply I have hurt you Now I’ll
pursue Your flawless Devine truth And I shut my eyes and thank You for Your
Mercy My tormented soul Lord You have calmed And I’m warm and safely rested in
Your arms </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>When you call on Jesus</title> <content>I’m So very ordinary
Nothing special on My own Oh I’ve never walked on water And I have never calmed
a storm Sometimes I’m hiding away from the madness around me Like a child who’s
afraid of the dark

But When I call on Jesus all things are possible I can mount on wings like
eagles’ and soar! When I call on Jesus Mountains are gonna fall ‘cause He’ll
move Heaven and earth to come rescue me when I call

La la la la la la la

Weary brother, broken daughter Little widow mother, you’re not alone If you’re
tired and scared of the madness around you if you cant find the strength to
carry on

When you call on Jesus All things are possible You can mount on wings like
eagles’ and soar! When You call on Jesus Mountains are gonna fall ‘Cause He’ll
move Heaven and earth to come rescue you when you call

Call Him in the Morning!...In the afternoon time! Late in the Evening ...He’ll
be there! When you’re heart is broken!..and you feel discouraged!... You can
just remember...that He’s there...He’ll be there!

When you call on Jesus All things are possible You can mount on wings like
eagles’ and soar! When You call on Jesus Mountains are gonna fall ‘Cause He’ll
move Heaven and earth to come rescue you when you call

When you call on Jesus All things are possible You can mount on wings like
eagles’ and soar! When You call on Jesus Mountains are gonna fall ‘Cause He’ll
move Heaven and earth to come rescue you when you call


La la la la la </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Everyday</title> <content>Everyday Under the cross I’d go and
kneel before you Lord And speak my thoughts Without fear Just like my Father I’d
say my inner feelings there When we’re together

Many times I had the thought Since that day, that when I grow There’s no way I
would get caught And forget Your Cross In my heart I’d always pray That my love
for You remains Not a thing would take away My need to see You My time to talk
to You

As I grew I reached for You But this time my hands were tied With something new
Sadness and fear Were both in me Locked up in sin and lust for a world Vain as
can be

Again that time I had to wonder How to start and sit back under Like the child
who felt that hunger Beneath Your Cross Then again my heart would pray That my
sins you’d wipe away Make my vital wish each day That I would see You To come
and talk to You

When I came I found You Father In Your wings I felt a warmth That’s like no
other You Dried My tears Renewed my soul And The deep regrets I had on You I
poured

I’m a humbled and in awe When I think of what I owe I will walk Your way for
sure Under Your Cross And my heart will sing to You All My life I’ll worship too
From my deepest and my true Love for the Cross…x2 My Love for Your Cross

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Lifted high (by the cross)</title> <content>At Thy feet O’ Lord I
lay and so There’s nowhere else I would rather go. Lift me up O’ Lord and and
let my spirit soar. Pour out Thy mercy through me and make me whole. {O’ Lord I
wish to leave this world I pray to thee and ask of You but one thing Lord I beg
of thee Tie my hands and flesh to Your Holy cross And let me not leave it at any
cost} x2 at any cost </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Je Penniot (Our Father)</title> <content>Je Penniot et khen
nifi-owi mareftovo enje Pekran. VERSE 1 When I wake up, at the break of day, Out
of bed I get up, to start the day, I clasp my hands together and say: Je Penniot
et khen nifi-owi mareftovo enje Pekran.

VERSE 2 After a full day of play, I come to the dinner table with the food on my
plate. And before the food gets cold, I lift my eyes and thank the Lord, For the
meal of this day, I lift my heart to pray, and say: Je Penniot et khen nifi-owi
mareftovo enje Pekran..

BRIDGE And as I come to end the day, I close my bedroom door to pray. And every
night down on my knees, I throw my cares down at Your feet. And I feel Your real
(Your real) Joy and Love You share, As I pray the Lord’s Prayer: Je Penniot et
khen nifi-owi mareftovo enje Pekran.

CHORUS 2 Our Father Who art in heaven, Hallowed and honoured be Thy name. CHORUS
3 Je Penniot et khen nifi-owi mareftovo enje Pekran. Mares-ee enje Tekmetoro. Je
Fok pe pi o-oo sha ne-eneh. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Hymn to the Virgin</title> <content>Let us sing a hymn To Mary the
Virgin That heavenly gate And Glory of our world The new bud of Human kind Who
gave birth to the Lord The Angels sing her song The Pride of the Church For she
received within No less than heaven The temple of our God Where He dwelt for
months

For she has put to down The wall of enmity Has brought about our peace And led
us to His throne Hold fast to her beauty The anchor of our faith And so take
heart All you people of God For He shall gird for war Against our many foes, Who
is the lover Of mankind </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Everything to me</title> <content>I grew up in sunday school I
memorized the Golden rule And how Jesus came to set the sinner free I know the
story inside out I can tell you all about The path that led Him up to Calvary
But ask me why He loves me And I don’t know what to say But i’ll never be the
same Because He changed my life when He became...

Everything to me He’s more than a story More than words on a page of history
He’s the air that I breath The water I thirst for And the ground beneath my feet
He’s everything, everything to me

We’re living in uncertain times And more and more I find that i’m aware Of just
how fragile life can be I want to tell the world I found A love that turned my
life around They need to know that they can taste and see Now everyday I’m
praying Just to give my heart away I want live for Jesus So that someone else
might see that He is...

Everything to me He’s more than a story More than words on a page of history
He’s the air that I breath The water I thirst for And the ground beneath my feet
He’s everything And looking back over my life at the end I’ll go to meet You
saying You’ve been...

Everything to me You’re more than a story More than words on a page of history
You’re everything to me You’re more than a story More than words on a page of
history You’re the air that I breath The water I thirst for And the ground
beneath my feet You’re everything to me Lord, you’re everything to me </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>You are amazing God</title> <content>From the highest of heights
to the depths of the sea Creation’s revealing Your majesty From the colours of
fall to the fragrance of spring Every creature unique in the song that it sings
All exclaiming Indescribable, uncontainable, You placed the stars in the sky and
You know them by name. You are amazing God All powerful, untameable, Awestruck
we fall to our knees as we humbly proclaim You are amazing God

Who has told every lightning bolt where it should go Or seen heavenly
storehouses laden with snow Who imagined the sun and gives source to its light
Yet conceals it to bring us the coolness of night None can fathom

Indescribable, uncontainable, You placed the stars in the sky and You know them
by name. You are amazing God All powerful, untameable, Awestruck we fall to our
knees as we humbly proclaim You are amazing God You are amazing God...........x2

You are amazing God Incomparable, unchangeable You see the depths of my heart
and You love me the same You are amazing God You are amazing God </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>The ship has come</title> <content>O look the ship has come And
sails come to unfold The captain there is calling All to Jesus Aboard I am going
to heaven I’m going to heaven So glad I’m with the saviour Going to heaven

O look the ship has come And in it sounds of praise The captain there is calling
O come without delay I am going to heaven I’m going to heaven So glad I’m with
the saviour Going to heaven.

Father in heaven how we love you We lift your Name in all the earth May your
kingdom be established in our praises As your people declare your mighty works
Blessed be the Lord God Almighty Who was and is and is to come Blessed be the
Lord God Almighty Who reigns forever more.......................x2 </content>
</hymn>



<hymn> <title>Who am I</title> <content>Who am I, that the Lord of all the earth
Would care to know my name Would care to feel my hurt Who am I, that the Bright
and Morning Star Would choose to light the way For my ever wandering heart

Not because of who I am But because of what You’ve done Not because of what I’ve
done But because of who You are

I am a flower quickly fading Here today and gone tomorrow A wave tossed in the
ocean Vapor in the wind Still You hear me when I’m calling Lord, You catch me
when I’m falling And You’ve told me who I am I am Yours, I am Yours

Who am I,that the eyes that see my sin Would look on me with love and watch me
rise again Who am I, that the voice that calmed the sea Would call out through
the rain And calm the storm in me

Not because of who I am But because of what You’ve done Not because of what I’ve
done But because of who You are

I am a flower quickly fading Here today and gone tomorrow A wave tossed in the
ocean Vapor in the wind Still You hear me when I’m calling Lord, You catch me
when I’m falling And You’ve told me who I am I am Yours, I am Yours </content>
</hymn>



<hymn> <title>Holy Queen</title> <content>Hail holy Queen enthroned above, Oh
Maria, Hail mother of Mercy and of Love, Oh Maria,

Triumph all ye cherubim! Sing with us ye seraphim! Heaven and Earth, resound the
hymn! Salve (salve), salve, salve Regina!

Hail holy Queen enthroned above, Oh Maria, Hail mother of Mercy and of Love, Oh
Maria,

Triumph all ye cherubim! Sing with us ye seraphim! Heaven and Earth, resound the
hymn! Salve (salve), salve, salve Regina!

Our life, our sweetness here below, Oh Maria, Our hope in sorrow and in woe Oh
Maria,

Triumph all ye cherubim! Sing with us ye seraphim! Heaven and Earth, resound the
hymn! Salve (salve), salve, salve Regina!

A-le-lu-iah Mater ad mater inter marata Sanctus sanctus dominus Virgo respice
mater ad spice Sanctus sanctus dominus A-le-lu-iah (A-le-lu-iah)

Our life, our sweetness here below, Oh Maria, Our hope in sorrow and in woe Oh
Maria,

Triumph all ye cherubim! Sing with us ye seraphim! Heaven and Earth, resound the
hymn! Salve (salve), salve, salve Regina!

Triumph all ye cherubim! Sing with us ye seraphim! Heaven and Earth, resound the
hymn! Salve (salve), salve, salve Regina! </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>As the thunder rolls</title> <content>I was sure by now,God, You
would have reached down and wiped our tears away, stepped in and saved the day.
But once again, I say amen and it’s still raining

as the thunder rolls I barely hear You whisper through the rain, “I’m with you”
and as Your mercy falls I raise my hands and praise the God who gives and takes
away.

And I’ll praise you in this storm and I will lift my hands for You are who You
are no matter where I am and every tear I’ve cried You hold in your hand You
never left my side and though my heart is torn I will praise You in this storm

I remember when I stumbled in the wind You heard my cry to You and raised me up
again my strength is almost gone how can I carry on if I can’t find You

as the thunder rolls I barely hear You whisper through the rain, “I’m with you”
and as Your mercy falls I raise my hands and praise the God who gives and takes
away.

I lift my eyes onto the hills where does my help come from? My help comes from
the Lord, the maker of heaven and earth I lift my eyes onto the hills where does
my help come from? My help comes from the Lord, the maker of heaven and earth

And I’ll praise you in this storm and I will lift my hands for You are who You
are no matter where I am and every tear I’ve cried You hold in your hand You
never left my side and though my heart is torn I will praise You in this storm

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Come, now is the time</title> <content>Come, now is the time to
worship Come, now is the time to give your heart Come, just as you are to
worship Come, just as you are before your God

One day ev’ry tongue will confess You are God One day ev’ry knee will bow Still
the greatest treause remains for those, Who gladly choose you now Come, now is
the time to worship Come, now is the time to give your heart Come, just as you
are to worship Come, just as you are before your God

One day ev’ry tongue will confess You are God One day ev’re knee will bow Still
the greates treasure remains for those, Who gladly choose you now Ooh, we’re
calling You Calling all nations Now is the time One day ev’ry tongue will
confess You are God One day ev’ry knee will bow Still the greatest treasure
remains for those, Who gladly choose you now One day ev’ry tongue will confess
You are God </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I called you</title> <content>I called upon You from the depth of
my heart, My Lord Jesus help me. Release from me the bonds of sin, My Lord Jesus
Christ help me. 2) Be a help to me so that you may save me, My Lord Jesus.. May
your goodness come to me speedily, My Lord Jesus Christ .... 3) Overshadow me
with the shadow of Your wings, My Lord Jesus.... In six days you have made all
the creation, My Lord Jesus Christ... 4) Seven times each day I will praise your
name, My Lord Jesus ... All the creation glorifies your Holy Name, My Lord Jesus
Christ ... 5) Yours is the Lordship and the power, My Lord Jesus .... Hasten O
my God and Save me, My Lord Jesus Christ ....

6) Every knee bows down before You, My Lord Jesus.. All the tongues bless your
Holy Name, My Lord Jesus Christ ... 7) Turn away your face from all my sins, My
Lord Jesus... Blot out O God all my iniquities, My Lord Jesus Christ .... 8) You
know my thoughts and search my inner parts, My Lord Jesus... Create in me a holy
heart, My Lord Jesus Christ ... 9) Your Holy Spirit cast not away from me, My
Lord Jesus... Incline Your ear to me and hear me speedily, My Lord Jesus Christ
... 10) Set before me a law in the way of Your righteousness, My Lord Jesus ...
Your Kingdom O my God is an everlasting Kingdom, My Lord Jesus Christ ... 11)
You are the Son of God I believe in You, My Lord Jesus ...

You who carries the sins of the world save me, My Lord Jesus Christ .. 12)
Forgive all of my sins, My Lord Jesus help me. All the souls together bless your
name, My Lord Jesus Christ help me. 13) Have patience on me and destroy me not
speedily, My Lord Jesus help me. I wake up at dawn that I may praise Your Name,
My Lord Jesus Christ ... 14) Your yoke is sweet and your burden is light, My
Lord Jesus.. Fulfil O Lord in the right time, My Lord Jesus Christ help me 15)
Praised and beloved is Your Holy Name, My Lord Jesus... Disperse from me all the
devils, My Lord Jesus Christ 16) Instil in me the fruit if Your righteousness,
My Lord Jesus.. .Give us Your true peace and forgive us our sins My Lord Jesus
Christ help me. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>A Babe Lies in the Cradle</title> <content>A babe lies in the
cradle, a little babe so dear, with noble light he shineth as shines a mirror
clear, this little babe so dear.

The babe within the cradle is Jesus Christ our Lord; to us all peace and amity
at this good time afford, thou Jesus Christ our Lord!

Whoso would rock the cradle where lies the gentle child, a lowly heart must lead
him, by passions undefiled, as Mary pure and mild.

O Jesus, babe beloved! O Jesus, babe divine! How mighty is thy wondrous love!
Fill thou this heart of mine with that great love of thine! </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>A Beautiful Life</title> <content>Each day I’ll do a golden deed,
By helping those who are in need; My life on earth is but a span, And so I’ll do
the best I can.

Refrain: Life’s evening sun is sinking low, A few more days, and I must go To
meet the deeds that I have done, Where there will be no setting sun.

To be a child of God each day, My light must shine along the way; I’ll sing His
praise while ages roll, And strive to help some troubled soul.

The only life that will endure, Is one that’s kind and good and pure; And so for
God I’ll take my stand, Each day I’ll lend a helping hand.

I’ll help someone in time of need, And journey on with rapid speed; I’ll help
the sick and poor and weak, And words of kindness to them speak.

While going down life’s weary road, I’ll try to lift some trav’ler’s load; I’ll
try to turn the night to day, Make flowers bloom along the way.</content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>A Debtor To Mercy Alone</title> <content>A debtor to mercy alone,
Of covenant mercy I sing, Nor fear, with God's righteousness on, My person and
off'rings to bring. The terrors of law and of God With me can have nothing to
do; My Savior's obedience and blood Hide all my transgressions from view.


2 The work which His goodness began, The arm of His strength will complete; His
promise is Yea and Amen, And never was forfeited yet. Things future, nor things
that are now, Not all things below or above, Can make Him His purpose forego, Or
sever my soul from His love.


3 My name from the palms of His hands Eternity will not erase; Imprest on His
heart, it remains In marks of indelible grace. Yes! I to the end shall endure,
As sure as the earnest is giv'n; More happy, but not more secure, When all
earthly ties have been riv'n.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>A Call To Prayer</title> <content>Softly the evening vespers
Hallow the closing day; Sweetly the Savior whispers, “Come to the throne and
pray.”

Refrain: Softly I hear Him calling, Calling at close of day; Sweetly His tones
are falling, “Come to the throne and pray.”

Come, ere the shadows lengthen, Bring Him thy burdened heart; Come where His
grace may strengthen, Come from thy cares apart.

Smiles of His love await thee, Lighting His lovely face; Just to behold His
beauty, Dwell in the secret place.

Boldly we may approach Him, Mercy and grace to own; Tempted like us, He bid us
Come to the Father’s throne. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Abide With Me</title> <content>The darkness deepens; Lord with me
abide. When other helpers fail and comforts flee, Help of the helpless, O abide
with me.

Swift to its close ebbs out life’s little day; Earth’s joys grow dim; its
glories pass away; Change and decay in all around I see; O Thou who changest
not, abide with me.

Not a brief glance I beg, a passing word; But as Thou dwell’st with Thy
disciples, Lord, Familiar, condescending, patient, free. Come not to sojourn,
but abide with me.

Come not in terrors, as the King of kings, But kind and good, with healing in
Thy wings, Tears for all woes, a heart for every plea— Come, Friend of sinners,
and thus bide with me.

Thou on my head in early youth didst smile; And, though rebellious and perverse
meanwhile, Thou hast not left me, oft as I left Thee, On to the close, O Lord,
abide with me.

I need Thy presence every passing hour. What but Thy grace can foil the
tempter’s power? Who, like Thyself, my guide and stay can be? Through cloud and
sunshine, Lord, abide with me.

I fear no foe, with Thee at hand to bless; Ills have no weight, and tears no
bitterness. Where is death’s sting? Where, grave, thy victory? I triumph still,
if Thou abide with me.

Hold Thou Thy cross before my closing eyes; Shine through the gloom and point me
to the skies. Heaven’s morning breaks, and earth’s vain shadows flee; In life,
in death, O Lord, abide with me.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All Hail the Power of Jesus' Name</title> <content>All hail the
power of Jesus’ Name! Let angels prostrate fall; Bring forth the royal diadem,
and crown Him Lord of all. Bring forth the royal diadem, and crown Him Lord of
all. Let highborn seraphs tune the lyre, and as they tune it, fall Before His
face Who tunes their choir, and crown Him Lord of all. Before His face Who tunes
their choir, and crown Him Lord of all.

Crown Him, ye morning stars of light, Who fixed this floating ball; Now hail the
strength of Israel’s might, and crown Him Lord of all. Now hail the strength of
Israel’s might, and crown Him Lord of all.

Crown Him, ye martyrs of your God, who from His altar call; Extol the Stem of
Jesse’s Rod, and crown Him Lord of all. Extol the Stem of Jesse’s Rod, and crown
Him Lord of all.

Ye seed of Israel’s chosen race, ye ransomed from the fall, Hail Him Who saves
you by His grace, and crown Him Lord of all. Hail Him Who saves you by His
grace, and crown Him Lord of all.

Hail Him, ye heirs of David’s line, Whom David Lord did call, The God incarnate,
Man divine, and crown Him Lord of all, The God incarnate, Man divine, and crown
Him Lord of all.

Sinners, whose love can ne’er forget the wormwood and the gall, Go spread your
trophies at His feet, and crown Him Lord of all. Go spread your trophies at His
feet, and crown Him Lord of all.

Let every tribe and every tongue before Him prostrate fall And shout in
universal song the crownèd Lord of all. And shout in universal song the crownèd
Lord of all </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All That I Am</title> <content>All that I am, all that I do All
that I ever have I offer now to You Take and sanctyfi these gifts For your
honour Lord Knowing that I love and serve You Is enough reward All that I dream
All that I pray All that I ever make I give to You today.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All Things Bright and Beautiful</title> <content>Refrain

All things bright and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise
and wonderful: The Lord God made them all.

Each little flower that opens, Each little bird that sings, He made their
glowing colors, He made their tiny wings.

Refrain

[Most hymnals omit the following verse]

The rich man in his castle, The poor man at his gate, He made them, high or
lowly, And ordered their estate.

Refrain

The purple headed mountains, The river running by, The sunset and the morning
That brightens up the sky.

Refrain

The cold wind in the winter, The pleasant summer sun, The ripe fruits in the
garden, He made them every one.

Refrain

The tall trees in the greenwood, The meadows where we play, The rushes by the
water, To gather every day.

Refrain

He gave us eyes to see them, And lips that we might tell How great is God
Almighty, Who has made all things well.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Alleluia</title> <content>Alleluia, Alleluia, Alleluia, Alleluia
Alleluia, Alleluia, Alleluia, Alleluia!

He’s my Savior! He’s my Savior! He’s my Savior!

He is Worthy! He is Worthy! He is Worthy!

I will Praise Him! I will Praise Him! I will Praise Him!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Ancient of Days</title> <content>Blessing and honor, glory and
power Be unto the Ancient of Days From every nation, all of creation, Bow before
the Ancient of Days

Every tongue in heaven and earth shall declare Your glory Every knee shall bow
at your throne in worship You will be exalted O God And Your kingdom shall not
pass away O Ancient of Days </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Are you washed in the blood?</title> <content>Have you been to
Jesus for the cleansing power? Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb? Are you
fully trusting in His grace this hour? Are you washed in the blood of the Lamb?
Refrain

Are you washed in the blood, In the soul cleansing blood of the Lamb? Are your
garments spotless? Are they white as snow? Are you washed in the blood of the
Lamb?

Are you walking daily by the Savior’s side? Are you washed in the blood of the
Lamb? Do you rest each moment in the Crucified? Are you washed in the blood of
the Lamb?

Refrain

When the Bridegroom cometh will your robes be white? Are you washed in the blood
of the Lamb? Will your soul be ready for the mansions bright, And be washed in
the blood of the Lamb?

Refrain

Lay aside the garments that are stained with sin, And be washed in the blood of
the Lamb; There’s a fountain flowing for the soul unclean, O be washed in the
blood of the Lamb!

Refrain </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>At Calvary</title> <content>Years I spent in vanity and pride,
Caring not my Lord was crucified, Knowing not it was for me He died on Calvary.
Refrain

Mercy there was great, and grace was free; Pardon there was multiplied to me;
There my burdened soul found liberty at Calvary.

By God’s Word at last my sin I learned; Then I trembled at the law I’d spurned,
Till my guilty soul imploring turned to Calvary.

Refrain

Now I’ve given to Jesus everything, Now I gladly own Him as my King, Now my
raptured soul can only sing of Calvary!

Refrain

Oh, the love that drew salvation’s plan! Oh, the grace that brought it down to
man! Oh, the mighty gulf that God did span at Calvary!

Refrain </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>At the Cross</title> <content>Alas! and did my Savior bleed And
did my Sovereign die? Would He devote that sacred head For sinners such as I?
Refrain At the cross, at the cross where I first saw the light, And the burden
of my heart rolled away, It was there by faith I received my sight, And now I am
happy all the day!

Thy body slain, sweet Jesus, Thine— And bathed in its own blood— While the firm
mark of wrath divine, His Soul in anguish stood.

Was it for crimes that I had done He groaned upon the tree? Amazing pity! grace
unknown! And love beyond degree!

Well might the sun in darkness hide And shut his glories in, When Christ, the
mighty Maker died, For man the creature’s sin.

Thus might I hide my blushing face While His dear cross appears, Dissolve my
heart in thankfulness, And melt my eyes to tears.

But drops of grief can ne’er repay The debt of love I owe: Here, Lord, I give my
self away ’Tis all that I can do. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Worthy</title> <content>(Vs1) Worthy, You are worthy King of
kings, Lord of lords You are worthy Worthy, You are worthy King of kings, Lord
of lords I worship You

(Vs2) Holy, You are holy King of kings, Lord of lords You are holy Holy, You are
holy King of kings, Lord of lords I worship You

(Vs3) Jesus, You are Jesus King of kings, Lord of lords You are Jesus Jesus, You
are Jesus King of kings, Lord of lords I worship You </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Ave Maria</title> <content>Ave Maria! blessed Maid! Lily of Eden's
fragrant shade! Who can express the love that nurtured thee, so pure and sweet,
making thy heart a shelter meet for Jesus' holy Dove!

Ave Maria! Mother blest, to whom, caressing and caressed, clings the eternal
Child; favored beyond Archangels' dream, when first on thee with tendered gleam
thy new-born Savior smiled.

Thou wept'st meek Maiden, Mother mild., thou wept'st upon thy sinless Child, thy
very heart was riven: and yet, what mourning matron here would deem thy sorrows
bought too dear by all on this side heaven!

A Son that never did amiss, that never shamed his Mother's kiss, nor crossed her
fondest prayer: e'en from the Tree he deigned to bow for her his agonized brow,
her, his sole earthly care.

Ave Maria! thou whose name all but adoring love may claim, yet may we reach thy
shrine; for he, thy Son and Savior, vows to crown all lowly lofty brows with
love and joy like thine. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Battle Hymn of the Republic</title> <content>Mine eyes have seen
the glory of the coming of the Lord; He is trampling out the vintage where the
grapes of wrath are stored; He hath loosed the fateful lightning of His terrible
swift sword; His truth is marching on. Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory!
Hallelujah! Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! His truth is marching on.

I have seen Him in the watch fires of a hundred circling camps They have builded
Him an altar in the evening dews and damps; I can read His righteous sentence by
the dim and flaring lamps; His day is marching on. Glory! Glory! Hallelujah!
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! His day is marching on.

I have read a fiery Gospel writ in burnished rows of steel; “As ye deal with My
contemners, so with you My grace shall deal”; Let the Hero, born of woman, crush
the serpent with His heel, Since God is marching on. Glory! Glory! Hallelujah!
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Since God is marching on.

He has sounded forth the trumpet that shall never call retreat; He is sifting
out the hearts of men before His judgment seat; Oh, be swift, my soul, to answer
Him! be jubilant, my feet; Our God is marching on. Glory! Glory! Hallelujah!
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Our God is marching on.

In the beauty of the lilies Christ was born across the sea, With a glory in His
bosom that transfigures you and me: As He died to make men holy, let us live to
make men free; [originally …let us die to make men free] While God is marching
on. Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory!
Hallelujah! While God is marching on.

He is coming like the glory of the morning on the wave, He is wisdom to the
mighty, He is honor to the brave; So the world shall be His footstool, and the
soul of wrong His slave, Our God is marching on. Glory! Glory! Hallelujah!
Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Glory! Glory! Hallelujah! Our God is marching
on.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Be Glorified</title> <content>In my life Lord, be glorified, be
glorified! In my life Lord, be glorified, be glorified today.

In Your church Lord, be glorified, be glorified! In Your church Lord, be
glorified, be glorified today.

In my home Lord, be glorified, be glorified! In my home Lord, be glorified, be
glorified today.

In my words Lord, be glorified, be glorified! In my words Lord, be glorified, be
glorified today.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Be Not Afraid</title> <content>“Be not afraid, ’tis I, ’tis I,
Though the storm rages wild; In thy sore need I’m passing by, Off’ring to help
thee, hear thy cry— Be of good cheer, My child.”

Refrain: “Be not afraid, ’tis I, Be not afraid, ’tis I”; Though wild winds
blowing, My bark o’erflowing, God rules in earth and sky: “Be not afraid, ’tis
I, Be not afraid, ’tis I”; The storm can’t harm my trusting soul, For Jesus
walks the waves that roll; His voice I hear, which calms my fear, “ ’Tis I, be
not afraid.”

Be not afraid, ’mid pressing foes, Jesus is watching near; He all thy deepest
sorrow knows, Walked every step thy pathway goes; Trust Him, then; do not fear.

Be not afraid, He knows thy heart, And He doth care for thee; Of all thy grief
He shares a part, Stands by thy side, He’ll not depart, If thou wilt faithful
be.

Be not afraid, O helpless one, Trust in His boundless grace; Say from the heart,
“Thy will be done, Finish the work Thou hast begun, Bring me to see Thy face.”
</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Be Still and Know That I Am God</title> <content>Be still and know
that I am God, be still and know that I am God, be still and know that I am God.

I am the Lord that healeth thee, I am the Lord that healeth thee, I am the Lord
that healeth thee.

In thee, O Lord, I put my trust, In thee, O Lord, I put my trust, In thee, O
Lord, I put my trust.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Be Thou My Vision</title> <content>Be Thou my Vision, O Lord of my
heart; Naught be all else to me, save that Thou art Thou my best Thought, by day
or by night, Waking or sleeping, Thy presence my light.

Be Thou my Wisdom, and Thou my true Word; I ever with Thee and Thou with me,
Lord; Thou my great Father, I Thy true son; Thou in me dwelling, and I with Thee
one.

Be Thou my battle Shield, Sword for the fight; Be Thou my Dignity, Thou my
Delight; Thou my soul’s Shelter, Thou my high Tower: Raise Thou me heavenward, O
Power of my power.

Riches I heed not, nor man’s empty praise, Thou mine Inheritance, now and
always: Thou and Thou only, first in my heart, High King of Heaven, my Treasure
Thou art.

High King of Heaven, my victory won, May I reach Heaven’s joys, O bright
Heaven’s Sun! Heart of my own heart, whatever befall, Still be my Vision, O
Ruler of all.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Day by Day</title> <content>Day by day, and with each passing
moment, Strength I find, to meet my trials here; Trusting in my Father’s wise
bestowment, I’ve no cause for worry or for fear. He Whose heart is kind beyond
all measure Gives unto each day what He deems best— Lovingly, its part of pain
and pleasure, Mingling toil with peace and rest.

Every day, the Lord Himself is near me With a special mercy for each hour; All
my cares He fain would bear, and cheer me, He Whose Name is Counselor and Power;
The protection of His child and treasure Is a charge that on Himself He laid;
“As thy days, thy strength shall be in measure,” This the pledge to me He made.

Help me then in every tribulation So to trust Thy promises, O Lord, That I lose
not faith’s sweet consolation Offered me within Thy holy Word. Help me, Lord,
when toil and trouble meeting, Ever to take, as from a father’s hand, One by
one, the days, the moments fleeting, Till I reach the promised land. </content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Faith of our Fathers</title> <content>Faith of our fathers, living
still, In spite of dungeon, fire and sword; O how our hearts beat high with joy
Whenever we hear that glorious Word! Refrain

Faith of our fathers, holy faith! We will be true to thee till death.

Faith of our fathers, we will strive To win all nations unto Thee; And through
the truth that comes from God, We all shall then be truly free.

Refrain

Faith of our fathers, we will love Both friend and foe in all our strife; And
preach Thee, too, as love knows how By kindly words and virtuous life.</content>
</hymn>

<hymn> <title>Glory To His Name</title> <content>Down at the cross where my
Savior died, Down where for cleansing from sin I cried, There to my heart was
the blood applied; Glory to His Name! Refrain

Glory to His Name, glory to His Name: There to my heart was the blood applied;
Glory to His Name!

I am so wondrously saved from sin, Jesus so sweetly abides within; There at the
cross where He took me in; Glory to His Name!

Refrain

Oh, precious fountain that saves from sin, I am so glad I have entered in; There
Jesus saves me and keeps me clean; Glory to His Name!

Refrain

Come to this fountain so rich and sweet, Cast thy poor soul at the Savior’s
feet; Plunge in today, and be made complete; Glory to His Name!

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>His Eye is on the Sparrow</title> <content>Why should I feel
discouraged, why should the shadows come, Why should my heart be lonely, and
long for heaven and home, When Jesus is my portion? My constant friend is He:
His eye is on the sparrow, and I know He watches me; His eye is on the sparrow,
and I know He watches me. Refrain

I sing because I’m happy, I sing because I’m free, For His eye is on the
sparrow, And I know He watches me.

“Let not your heart be troubled,” His tender word I hear, And resting on His
goodness, I lose my doubts and fears; Though by the path He leadeth, but one
step I may see; His eye is on the sparrow, and I know He watches me; His eye is
on the sparrow, and I know He watches me.

Refrain

Whenever I am tempted, whenever clouds arise, When songs give place to sighing,
when hope within me dies, I draw the closer to Him, from care He sets me free;
His eye is on the sparrow, and I know He watches me; His eye is on the sparrow,
and I know He watches me.

Refrain

</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>In The Garden</title> <content>I come to the garden alone While
the dew is still on the roses And the voice I hear falling on my ear The Son of
God discloses. Refrain

And He walks with me, and He talks with me, And He tells me I am His own; And
the joy we share as we tarry there, None other has ever known.

He speaks, and the sound of His voice, Is so sweet the birds hush their singing,
And the melody that He gave to me Within my heart is ringing.

Refrain

I’d stay in the garden with Him Though the night around me be falling, But He
bids me go; through the voice of woe His voice to me is calling.

Refrain </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Love Lifted Me</title> <content>I was sinking deep in sin, far
from the peaceful shore, Very deeply stained within, sinking to rise no more,
But the Master of the sea, heard my despairing cry, From the waters lifted me,
now safe am I. Refrain

Love lifted me! Love lifted me! When nothing else could help Love lifted me!

All my heart to Him I give, ever to Him I’ll cling In His blessèd presence live,
ever His praises sing, Love so mighty and so true, merits my soul’s best songs,
Faithful, loving service too, to Him belongs.

Refrain

Souls in danger look above, Jesus completely saves, He will lift you by His
love, out of the angry waves. He’s the Master of the sea, billows His will obey,
He your Savior wants to be, be saved today.

Refrain </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>O How I Love Jesus</title> <content>There is a name I love to
hear, I love to sing its worth, It sounds like music in the ear, The sweetest
name on earth.

O how I love Jesus, O how I love Jesus, O how I love Jesus, Because He first
loved me.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>The Lord's My Shepherd</title> <content>The Lord’s my Shepherd,
I’ll not want; He makes me down to lie In pastures green; He leadeth me The
quiet waters by.

My soul He doth restore again, And me to walk doth make Within the paths of
righteousness, E’en for His own name’s sake.

Yea, though I walk in death’s dark vale, Yet will I fear no ill; For Thou art
with me, and Thy rod And staff my comfort still.

My table Thou hast furnished me In presence of my foes; My head Thou dost with
oil anoint, And my cup overflows.

Goodness and mercy all my life Shall surely follow me; And in God’s house
forevermore, My dwelling place shall be. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Who Put the Colors in the Rainbow</title> <content>Who put the
colors in the rainbow? Who put the salt into the sea? Who put the cold into the
snowflake? Who made you and me? Who put the hump upon the camel? Who put the
neck on the giraffe? Who put the tail upon the monkey? Who made hyenas laugh?
Who made whales and snails and quails? Who made hogs and dogs and frogs? Who
made bats and rats and cats? Who made everything?</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Turn Your Eyes Upon Jesus</title> <content>O soul, are you weary
and troubled? No light in the darkness you see? There’s a light for a look at
the Savior, And life more abundant and free!

Refrain

Turn your eyes upon Jesus, Look full in His wonderful face, And the things of
earth will grow strangely dim, In the light of His glory and grace.

Through death into life everlasting He passed, and we follow Him there; Over us
sin no more hath dominion— For more than conquerors we are!

Refrain

His Word shall not fail you—He promised; Believe Him, and all will be well: Then
go to a world that is dying, His perfect salvation to tell!

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jerusalem Hymn</title> <content>And did those feet in ancient time
Walk upon England's mountain green? And was the holy Lamb of God On England's
pleasant pastures seen? And did the countenance divine Shine forth upon our
clouded hills? And was Jerusalem builded here Among those dark satanic mills?

Bring me my bow of burning gold! Bring me my arrows of desire! Bring me my
spear! O clouds, unfold! Bring me my chariot of fire! I will not cease from
mental fight, Nor shall my sword sleep in my hand, Till we have built Jerusalem
In England's green and pleasant land.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Holy Holy Holy </title> <content>Holy, holy, holy! Lord God
Almighty! Early in the morning our song shall rise to Thee; Holy, holy, holy,
merciful and mighty! God in three Persons, blessèd Trinity!

Holy, holy, holy! All the saints adore Thee, Casting down their golden crowns
around the glassy sea; Cherubim and seraphim falling down before Thee, Who was,
and is, and evermore shall be.

Holy, holy, holy! though the darkness hide Thee, Though the eye of sinful man
Thy glory may not see; Only Thou art holy; there is none beside Thee, Perfect in
power, in love, and purity.

Holy, holy, holy! Lord God Almighty! All Thy works shall praise Thy Name, in
earth, and sky, and sea; Holy, holy, holy; merciful and mighty! God in three
Persons, blessèd Trinity!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>How Great Thou Art</title> <content>Lord my God! When I in awesome
wonder Consider all the works thy hand hath made, I see the stars, I hear the
mighty thunder, Thy power throughout the universe displayed;

Refrain: Then sings my soul, my Saviour God, to Thee, How great Thou art, how
great Thou art! Then sings my soul, my Saviour God, to Thee, How great Thou art,
how great Thou art!

When through the woods and forest glades I wander and hear the birds sing
sweetly in the trees; when I look down from lofty mountain grandeur, and hear
the brook, and feel he gentle breeze;

Refrain

And when I think that God his son not sparing, Sent him to die - I scarce can
take it in, That on the cross my burden gladly bearing, He bled and died to take
away my sin:

Refrain

When Christ shall come with shout of acclamation And take me home- what joy
shall fill my heart! Then I shall bow in humble adoration And there proclaim, my
God, how great thou art!

Then sings my soul, my Saviour God, to Thee, How great Thou art, how great Thou
art! Then sings my soul, my Saviour God, to Thee, How great Thou art, how great
Thou art!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Be Thou My Vision</title> <content>Be Thou my Vision, O Lord of my
heart; Naught be all else to me, save that Thou art Thou my best Thought, by day
or by night, Waking or sleeping, Thy presence my light.

Be Thou my Wisdom, and Thou my true Word; I ever with Thee and Thou with me,
Lord; Thou my great Father, I Thy true son; Thou in me dwelling, and I with Thee
one.

Be Thou my battle Shield, Sword for the fight; Be Thou my Dignity, Thou my
Delight; Thou my soul’s Shelter, Thou my high Tower: Raise Thou me heavenward, O
Power of my power.

Riches I heed not, nor man’s empty praise, Thou mine Inheritance, now and
always: Thou and Thou only, first in my heart, High King of Heaven, my Treasure
Thou art.

High King of Heaven, my victory won, May I reach Heaven’s joys, O bright
Heaven’s Sun! Heart of my own heart, whatever befall, Still be my Vision, O
Ruler of all.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Rock Of Ages</title> <content>Rock of Ages, cleft for me, Let me
hide myself in Thee; Let the water and the blood, From Thy wounded side which
flowed, Be of sin the double cure; Save from wrath and make me pure.

Not the labor of my hands Can fulfill Thy law’s demands; Could my zeal no
respite know, Could my tears forever flow, All for sin could not atone; Thou
must save, and Thou alone.

Nothing in my hand I bring, Simply to the cross I cling; Naked, come to Thee for
dress; Helpless look to Thee for grace; Foul, I to the fountain fly; Wash me,
Savior, or I die.

While I draw this fleeting breath, When mine eyes shall close in death, When I
soar to worlds unknown, See Thee on Thy judgment throne, Rock of Ages, cleft for
me, Let me hide myself in Thee</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Joyful Joyful </title> <content>Joyful, joyful, we adore Thee, God
of glory, Lord of love; Hearts unfold like flowers before Thee, opening to the
sun above. Melt the clouds of sin and sadness; drive the dark of doubt away;
Giver of immortal gladness, fill us with the light of day!

All Thy works with joy surround Thee, earth and heaven reflect Thy rays, Stars
and angels sing around Thee, center of unbroken praise. Field and forest, vale
and mountain, flowery meadow, flashing sea, Singing bird and flowing fountain
call us to rejoice in Thee.

Thou art giving and forgiving, ever blessing, ever blessed, Wellspring of the
joy of living, ocean depth of happy rest! Thou our Father, Christ our Brother,
all who live in love are Thine; Teach us how to love each other, lift us to the
joy divine.

Mortals, join the happy chorus, which the morning stars began; Father love is
reigning o’er us, brother love binds man to man. Ever singing, march we onward,
victors in the midst of strife, Joyful music leads us Sunward in the triumph
song of life.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>It Is Well With My Soul</title> <content>When peace, like a river,
attendeth my way, When sorrows like sea billows roll; Whatever my lot, Thou has
taught me to say, It is well, it is well, with my soul.

Refrain

It is well, with my soul, It is well, with my soul, It is well, it is well, with
my soul.

Though Satan should buffet, though trials should come, Let this blest assurance
control, That Christ has regarded my helpless estate, And hath shed His own
blood for my soul.

Refrain

My sin, oh, the bliss of this glorious thought! My sin, not in part but the
whole, Is nailed to the cross, and I bear it no more, Praise the Lord, praise
the Lord, O my soul!

Refrain

For me, be it Christ, be it Christ hence to live: If Jordan above me shall roll,
No pang shall be mine, for in death as in life Thou wilt whisper Thy peace to my
soul.

Refrain

But, Lord, ‘tis for Thee, for Thy coming we wait, The sky, not the grave, is our
goal; Oh trump of the angel! Oh voice of the Lord! Blessèd hope, blessèd rest of
my soul!

Refrain

And Lord, haste the day when my faith shall be sight, The clouds be rolled back
as a scroll; The trump shall resound, and the Lord shall descend, Even so, it is
well with my soul.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>In The Garden</title> <content>I come to the garden alone While
the dew is still on the roses And the voice I hear falling on my ear The Son of
God discloses.

Refrain

And He walks with me, and He talks with me, And He tells me I am His own; And
the joy we share as we tarry there, None other has ever known.

He speaks, and the sound of His voice, Is so sweet the birds hush their singing,
And the melody that He gave to me Within my heart is ringing.

Refrain

I’d stay in the garden with Him Though the night around me be falling, But He
bids me go; through the voice of woe His voice to me is calling.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>This Little Light Of Mine</title> <content>This little light of
mine, I'm gonna let it shine. This little light of mine, I'm gonna let it shine,
let it shine, let it shine, let it shine.

Won't let Satan blow it out. I'm gonna let it shine. Won't let Satan blow it
out. I'm gonna let it shine, let it shine, let it shine, let it shine.

Let it shine til Jesus comes. I'm gonna let it shine. Let it shine til Jesus
comes. I'm gonna let it shine, let it shine, let it shine, let it shine.

Hide it under a bushel - NO! I'm gonna let it shine. Hide it under a bushel -
NO! I'm gonna let it shine, Let it shine, let it shine, let it shine.

Let it shine over the whole wide world, I'm gonna let it shine. Let it shine
over the whole wide world, I'm gonna let it shine, let it shine, let it shine,
let it shine.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Just A Closer Walk With Thee</title> <content>I am weak, but Thou
art strong; Jesus, keep me from all wrong; I’ll be satisfied as long As I walk,
let me walk close to Thee.

Refrain

Just a closer walk with Thee, Grant it, Jesus, is my plea, Daily walking close
to Thee, Let it be, dear Lord, let it be.

Through this world of toil and snares, If I falter, Lord, who cares? Who with me
my burden shares? None but Thee, dear Lord, none but Thee.

Refrain

When my feeble life is o’er, Time for me will be no more; Guide me gently,
safely o’er To Thy kingdom shore, to Thy shore.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Hallelujah Chorus</title> <content>Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah! For the Lord God Omnipotent reigneth.
Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah!

For the Lord God omnipotent reigneth. Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah!

The kingdom of this world Is become the kingdom of our Lord, And of His Christ,
and of His Christ; And He shall reign for ever and ever, For ever and ever,
forever and ever,

King of kings, and Lord of lords, King of kings, and Lord of lords, And Lord of
lords, And He shall reign, And He shall reign forever and ever, King of kings,
forever and ever, And Lord of lords, Hallelujah! Hallelujah!

And He shall reign forever and ever, King of kings! and Lord of lords! And He
shall reign forever and ever, King of kings! and Lord of lords! Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Nearer My God To Thee</title> <content>Nearer, my God, to Thee,
nearer to Thee! E’en though it be a cross that raiseth me, Still all my song
shall be, nearer, my God, to Thee.

Refrain

Nearer, my God, to Thee, Nearer to Thee!

Though like the wanderer, the sun gone down, Darkness be over me, my rest a
stone. Yet in my dreams I’d be nearer, my God to Thee.

Refrain

There let the way appear, steps unto Heav’n; All that Thou sendest me, in mercy
given; Angels to beckon me nearer, my God, to Thee.

Refrain

Then, with my waking thoughts bright with Thy praise, Out of my stony griefs
Bethel I’ll raise; So by my woes to be nearer, my God, to Thee.

Refrain

Or, if on joyful wing cleaving the sky, Sun, moon, and stars forgot, upward I’ll
fly, Still all my song shall be, nearer, my God, to Thee.

Refrain

There in my Father’s home, safe and at rest, There in my Savior’s love,
perfectly blest; Age after age to be, nearer my God to Thee.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Blessed Assurance</title> <content>Blessed assurance, Jesus is
mine! O what a foretaste of glory divine! Heir of salvation, purchase of God,
Born of His Spirit, washed in His blood.

Refrain

This is my story, this is my song, Praising my Savior, all the day long; This is
my story, this is my song, Praising my Savior, all the day long.

Perfect submission, perfect delight, Visions of rapture now burst on my sight;
Angels descending bring from above Echoes of mercy, whispers of love.

Refrain

Perfect submission, all is at rest I in my Savior am happy and blest, Watching
and waiting, looking above, Filled with His goodness, lost in His love.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>23rd Psalm</title> <content>The Lord's my shepherd, I'll not want;
He makes me down to lie In pastures green; he leadeth me The quiet waters by.

My soul he doth restore again, And me to walk doth make Within the paths of
righteousness, E'en for his own name's sake.

Yea, though I walk in death's dark vale, Yet will I fear no ill: For thou art
with me, and thy rod And staff me comfort still.

My table thou hast furnished In prsence of my foes; My head thou dost with oil
anoint And my cup overflows.

Goodness and mercy all my life Shall surely follow me; And in God's house for
evermore My dwelling-place shall be.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>The Old Rugged Cross</title> <content>On a hill far away stood an
old rugged cross, The emblem of suffering and shame; And I love that old cross
where the dearest and best For a world of lost sinners was slain.

Refrain

So I’ll cherish the old rugged cross, Till my trophies at last I lay down; I
will cling to the old rugged cross, And exchange it some day for a crown.

O that old rugged cross, so despised by the world, Has a wondrous attraction for
me; For the dear Lamb of God left His glory above To bear it to dark Calvary.

Refrain

In that old rugged cross, stained with blood so divine, A wondrous beauty I see,
For ’twas on that old cross Jesus suffered and died, To pardon and sanctify me.

Refrain

To the old rugged cross I will ever be true; Its shame and reproach gladly bear;
Then He’ll call me some day to my home far away, Where His glory forever I’ll
share.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Abide With Me</title> <content>Abide with me; fast falls the
eventide; The darkness deepens; Lord with me abide. When other helpers fail and
comforts flee, Help of the helpless, O abide with me.

Swift to its close ebbs out life’s little day; Earth’s joys grow dim; its
glories pass away; Change and decay in all around I see; O Thou who changest
not, abide with me.

Not a brief glance I beg, a passing word; But as Thou dwell’st with Thy
disciples, Lord, Familiar, condescending, patient, free. Come not to sojourn,
but abide with me.

Come not in terrors, as the King of kings, But kind and good, with healing in
Thy wings, Tears for all woes, a heart for every plea— Come, Friend of sinners,
and thus bide with me.

Thou on my head in early youth didst smile; And, though rebellious and perverse
meanwhile, Thou hast not left me, oft as I left Thee, On to the close, O Lord,
abide with me.

I need Thy presence every passing hour. What but Thy grace can foil the
tempter’s power? Who, like Thyself, my guide and stay can be? Through cloud and
sunshine, Lord, abide with me.

I fear no foe, with Thee at hand to bless; Ills have no weight, and tears no
bitterness. Where is death’s sting? Where, grave, thy victory? I triumph still,
if Thou abide with me.

Hold Thou Thy cross before my closing eyes; Shine through the gloom and point me
to the skies. Heaven’s morning breaks, and earth’s vain shadows flee; In life,
in death, O Lord, abide with me.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>To God Be The Glory</title> <content>To God be the glory, great
things He has done; So loved He the world that He gave us His Son, Who yielded
His life an atonement for sin, And opened the life gate that all may go in.

Refrain

Praise the Lord, praise the Lord, Let the earth hear His voice! Praise the Lord,
praise the Lord, Let the people rejoice! O come to the Father, through Jesus the
Son, And give Him the glory, great things He has done.

O perfect redemption, the purchase of blood, To every believer the promise of
God; The vilest offender who truly believes, That moment from Jesus a pardon
receives.

Refrain

Great things He has taught us, great things He has done, And great our rejoicing
through Jesus the Son; But purer, and higher, and greater will be Our wonder,
our transport, when Jesus we see.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>What A Friend We Have In Jesus</title> <content>What a friend we
have in Jesus, all our sins and griefs to bear! What a privilege to carry
everything to God in prayer! O what peace we often forfeit, O what needless pain
we bear, all because we do not carry everything to God in prayer.

Have we trials and temptations? Is there trouble anywhere? We should never be
discouraged; take it to the Lord in prayer. Can we find a friend so faithful who
will all our sorrows share? Jesus knows our every weakness; take it to the Lord
in prayer.

Are we weak and heavy laden, cumbered with a load of care? Precious Savior,
still our refuge; take it to the Lord in prayer. Do thy friends despise, forsake
thee? Take it to the Lord in prayer! In his arms he'll take and shield thee;
thou wilt find a solace there.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus Lover Of My Soul</title> <content>Jesus, lover of my soul,
let me to Thy bosom fly, While the nearer waters roll, while the tempest still
is high. Hide me, O my Savior, hide, till the storm of life is past; Safe into
the haven guide; O receive my soul at last.

Other refuge have I none, hangs my helpless soul on Thee; Leave, ah! leave me
not alone, still support and comfort me. All my trust on Thee is stayed, all my
help from Thee I bring; Cover my defenseless head with the shadow of Thy wing.

Wilt Thou not regard my call? Wilt Thou not accept my prayer? Lo! I sink, I
faint, I fall - Lo! on Thee I cast my care; Reach me out Thy gracious hand!
While I of Thy strength receive, Hoping against hope I stand, dying, and behold,
I live.

Thou, O Christ, art all I want, more than all in Thee I find; Raise the fallen,
cheer the faint, heal the sick, and lead the blind. Just and holy is Thy Name, I
am all unrighteousness; False and full of sin I am; Thou art full of truth and
grace.

Plenteous grace with Thee is found, grace to cover all my sin; Let the healing
streams abound; make and keep me pure within. Thou of life the fountain art,
freely let me take of Thee; Spring Thou up within my heart; rise to all
eternity.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Breath Of God</title> <content>Breathe on me, breath of God, Fill
me with life anew, That I may love what Thou dost love, And do what Thou wouldst
do.

Breathe on me, breath of God, Until my heart is pure, Until with Thee I will one
will, To do and to endure.

Breathe on me, breath of God, Blend all my soul with Thine, Until this earthly
part of me Glows with Thy fire divine.

Breathe on me, breath of God, So shall I never die, But live with Thee the
perfect life Of Thine eternity.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>The Holy City</title> <content>Last night I lay a-sleeping There
came a dream so fair, I stood in old Jerusalem Beside the temple there. I heard
the children singing, And ever as they sang, Me thought the voice of angels From
heaven in answer rang.

Jerusalem! Jerusalem! Lift up your gates and sing, Hosanna in the highest!
Hosanna to your King!

And then me thought my dream was changed, The streets no longer rang, Hushed
were the glad Hosannas The little children sang. The sun grew dark with mystery,
The morn was cold and chill, As the shadow of a cross arose Upon a lonely hill.

Jerusalem! Jerusalem! Hark! How the angels sing, Hosanna in the highest! Hosanna
to your King!

And once again the scene was changed; New earth there seemed to be; I saw the
Holy City Beside the tideless sea; The light of God was on its streets, The
gates were open wide, And all who would might enter, And no one was denied. No
need of moon or stars by night, Or sun to shine by day; It was the new Jerusalem
That would not pass away.

Jerusalem! Jerusalem! Sing for the night is o'er! Hosanna in the highest!
Hosanna for evermore!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Breathe On Me Breath Of God</title> <content>Breathe on me, breath
of God, Fill me with life anew, That I may love what Thou dost love, And do what
Thou wouldst do.

Breathe on me, breath of God, Until my heart is pure, Until with Thee I will one
will, To do and to endure.

Breathe on me, breath of God, Blend all my soul with Thine, Until this earthly
part of me Glows with Thy fire divine.

Breathe on me, breath of God, So shall I never die, But live with Thee the
perfect life Of Thine eternity.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Fight The Good Fight</title> <content>Fight the good fight with
all thy might; Christ is thy Strength, and Christ thy Right; Lay hold on life,
and it shall be Thy joy and crown eternally.

Run the straight race through God’s good grace, Lift up thine eyes, and seek His
face; Life with its way before us lies, Christ is the Path, and Christ the
Prize.

Cast care aside, upon thy Guide, Lean, and His mercy will provide; Lean, and the
trusting soul shall prove Christ is its Life, and Christ its Love.

Faint not nor fear, His arms are near, He changeth not, and thou art dear. Only
believe, and thou shalt see That Christ is all in all to thee.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus Paid It All</title> <content>I hear the Savior say, “Thy
strength indeed is small; Child of weakness, watch and pray, Find in Me thine
all in all.”

Refrain

Jesus paid it all, All to Him I owe; Sin had left a crimson stain, He washed it
white as snow.

For nothing good have I Whereby Thy grace to claim, I’ll wash my garments white
In the blood of Calv’ry’s Lamb.

Refrain

And now complete in Him My robe His righteousness, Close sheltered ’neath His
side, I am divinely blest.

Refrain

Lord, now indeed I find Thy power and Thine alone, Can change the leper’s spots
And melt the heart of stone.

Refrain

When from my dying bed My ransomed soul shall rise, “Jesus died my soul to
save,” Shall rend the vaulted skies.

Refrain

And when before the throne I stand in Him complete, I’ll lay my trophies down
All down at Jesus’ feet.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus Christ Is Risen Today</title> <content>Christ, the Lord, is
risen today, Alleluia! Sons of men and angels say, Alleluia! Raise your joys and
triumphs high, Alleluia! Sing, ye heavens, and earth, reply, Alleluia!

Love’s redeeming work is done, Alleluia! Fought the fight, the battle won,
Alleluia! Lo! the Sun’s eclipse is over, Alleluia! Lo! He sets in blood no more,
Alleluia!

Vain the stone, the watch, the seal, Alleluia! Christ hath burst the gates of
hell, Alleluia! Death in vain forbids His rise, Alleluia! Christ hath opened
paradise, Alleluia!

Lives again our glorious King, Alleluia! Where, O death, is now thy sting?
Alleluia! Once He died our souls to save, Alleluia! Where thy victory, O grave?
Alleluia!

Soar we now where Christ hath led, Alleluia! Following our exalted Head,
Alleluia! Made like Him, like Him we rise, Alleluia! Ours the cross, the grave,
the skies, Alleluia!

Hail, the Lord of earth and heaven, Alleluia! Praise to Thee by both be given,
Alleluia! Thee we greet triumphant now, Alleluia! Hail, the resurrection day,
Alleluia!

King of glory, Soul of bliss, Alleluia! Everlasting life is this, Alleluia! Thee
to know, Thy power to prove, Alleluia! Thus to sing and thus to love, Alleluia!

Hymns of praise then let us sing, Alleluia! Unto Christ, our heavenly King,
Alleluia! Who endured the cross and grave, Alleluia! Sinners to redeem and save.
Alleluia!

But the pains that He endured, Alleluia! Our salvation have procured, Alleluia!
Now above the sky He’s King, Alleluia! Where the angels ever sing. Alleluia!

Jesus Christ is risen today, Alleluia! Our triumphant holy day, Alleluia! Who
did once upon the cross, Alleluia! Suffer to redeem our loss.
Alleluia!</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Fairest Lord Jesus</title> <content>Fairest Lord Jesus, Ruler of
all nature, O Thou of God and man the Son, Thee will I cherish, Thee will I
honor, Thou, my soul’s glory, joy and crown.

Fair are the meadows, fairer still the woodlands, Robed in the blooming garb of
spring; Jesus is fairer, Jesus is purer, Who makes the woeful heart to sing.

Fair is the sunshine, Fairer still the moonlight, And all the twinkling starry
host; Jesus shines brighter, Jesus shines purer Than all the angels heaven can
boast.

All fairest beauty, heavenly and earthly, Wondrously, Jesus, is found in Thee;
None can be nearer, fairer or dearer, Than Thou, my Savior, art to me.

Beautiful Savior! Lord of all the nations! Son of God and Son of Man! Glory and
honor, praise, adoration, Now and forever more be Thine.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>For The Beauty Of The Earth</title> <content>For the beauty of the
earth, For the beauty of the skies, For the love which from our birth Over and
around us lies, Lord of all, to thee we raise This our grateful hymn of praise.

For the beauty of each hour Of the day and of the night, Hill and vale, and tree
and flower, Sun and moon and stars of light, Lord of all, to thee we raise This
our grateful hymn of praise.

For the joy of human love, Brother, sister, parent, child, Friends on earth, and
friends above, Pleasures pure and undefiled, Lord of all, to thee we raise This
our grateful hymn of praise.

For each perfect gift of thine, To our race so freely given, Graces human and
divine, Flowers of earth and buds of heaven, Lord of all, to thee we raise This
our grateful hymn of praise.

For thy Church which evermore Lifteth holy hands above, Offering up on every
shore Her pure sacrifice of love, Lord of all, to thee we raise This our
grateful hymn of praise.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Shall We Gather At The River?</title> <content>Shall we gather at
the river, Where bright angel feet have trod, With its crystal tide forever
Flowing by the throne of God?

Refrain

Yes, we’ll gather at the river, The beautiful, the beautiful river; Gather with
the saints at the river That flows by the throne of God.

On the margin of the river, Washing up its silver spray, We will talk and
worship ever, All the happy golden day.

Refrain

Ere we reach the shining river, Lay we every burden down; Grace our spirits will
deliver, And provide a robe and crown.

Refrain

At the smiling of the river, Mirror of the Savior’s face, Saints, whom death
will never sever, Lift their songs of saving grace.

Refrain

Soon we’ll reach the silver river, Soon our pilgrimage will cease; Soon our
happy hearts will quiver With the melody of peace.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All Hail The Power Of Jesus Name</title> <content>All hail the
power of Jesus’ Name! Let angels prostrate fall; Bring forth the royal diadem,
and crown Him Lord of all. Bring forth the royal diadem, and crown Him Lord of
all.

Let highborn seraphs tune the lyre, and as they tune it, fall Before His face
Who tunes their choir, and crown Him Lord of all. Before His face Who tunes
their choir, and crown Him Lord of all.

Crown Him, ye morning stars of light, Who fixed this floating ball; Now hail the
strength of Israel’s might, and crown Him Lord of all. Now hail the strength of
Israel’s might, and crown Him Lord of all.

Crown Him, ye martyrs of your God, who from His altar call; Extol the Stem of
Jesse’s Rod, and crown Him Lord of all. Extol the Stem of Jesse’s Rod, and crown
Him Lord of all.

Ye seed of Israel’s chosen race, ye ransomed from the fall, Hail Him Who saves
you by His grace, and crown Him Lord of all. Hail Him Who saves you by His
grace, and crown Him Lord of all.

Hail Him, ye heirs of David’s line, Whom David Lord did call, The God incarnate,
Man divine, and crown Him Lord of all, The God incarnate, Man divine, and crown
Him Lord of all.

Sinners, whose love can ne’er forget the wormwood and the gall, Go spread your
trophies at His feet, and crown Him Lord of all. Go spread your trophies at His
feet, and crown Him Lord of all.

Let every tribe and every tongue before Him prostrate fall And shout in
universal song the crownèd Lord of all. And shout in universal song the crownèd
Lord of all.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Crown Him With Many Crowns</title> <content>Crown Him with many
crowns, the Lamb upon His throne. Hark! How the heavenly anthem drowns all music
but its own. Awake, my soul, and sing of Him who died for thee, And hail Him as
thy matchless King through all eternity.

Crown Him the virgin’s Son, the God incarnate born, Whose arm those crimson
trophies won which now His brow adorn; Fruit of the mystic rose, as of that rose
the stem; The root whence mercy ever flows, the Babe of Bethlehem.

Crown Him the Son of God, before the worlds began, And ye who tread where He
hath trod, crown Him the Son of Man; Who every grief hath known that wrings the
human breast, And takes and bears them for His own, that all in Him may rest.

Crown Him the Lord of life, who triumphed over the grave, And rose victorious in
the strife for those He came to save. His glories now we sing, Who died, and
rose on high, Who died eternal life to bring, and lives that death may die.

Crown Him the Lord of peace, Whose power a scepter sways From pole to pole, that
wars may cease, and all be prayer and praise. His reign shall know no end, and
round His piercèd feet Fair flowers of paradise extend their fragrance ever
sweet.

Crown Him the Lord of love, behold His hands and side, Those wounds, yet visible
above, in beauty glorified. No angel in the sky can fully bear that sight, But
downward bends his burning eye at mysteries so bright.

Crown Him the Lord of Heaven, enthroned in worlds above, Crown Him the King to
Whom is given the wondrous name of Love. Crown Him with many crowns, as thrones
before Him fall; Crown Him, ye kings, with many crowns, for He is King of all.

Crown Him the Lord of lords, who over all doth reign, Who once on earth, the
incarnate Word, for ransomed sinners slain, Now lives in realms of light, where
saints with angels sing Their songs before Him day and night, their God,
Redeemer, King.

Crown Him the Lord of years, the Potentate of time, Creator of the rolling
spheres, ineffably sublime. All hail, Redeemer, hail! For Thou has died for me;
Thy praise and glory shall not fail throughout eternity.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>The King Of Love My Shepherd Is</title> <content>The king of love
my shepherd is, Whose goodness faileth never; I nothing lack if I am his And he
is mine for ever.

Where streams of living water flow My ransomed soul he leadeth, And where the
verdant pastures grow With food celestial feedeth.

Perverse and foolish oft I strayed, But yet in love he sought me, And on his
shoulder gently laid, And home rejoicing brought me.

In death's dark vale I fear no ill With thee, dear Lord, beside me; Thy rod and
staff my comfort still, Thy cross before to guide me.

Thou spread'st a table in my sight; Thy unction grace bestoweth; And O what
transport of delight From thy pure chalice floweth!

And so through all the length of days Thy goodness faileth never: Good shepherd,
may I sing thy praise Within thy house for ever.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Take My Life And Let It Be</title> <content>Take my life, and let
it be consecrated, Lord, to Thee. Take my moments and my days; let them flow in
ceaseless praise. Take my hands, and let them move at the impulse of Thy love.
Take my feet, and let them be swift and beautiful for Thee.

Take my voice, and let me sing always, only, for my King. Take my lips, and let
them be filled with messages from Thee. Take my silver and my gold; not a mite
would I withhold. Take my intellect, and use every power as Thou shalt choose.

Take my will, and make it Thine; it shall be no longer mine. Take my heart, it
is Thine own; it shall be Thy royal throne. Take my love, my Lord, I pour at Thy
feet its treasure store. Take myself, and I will be ever, only, all for
Thee.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Jesus Loves Me This I Know</title> <content>Jesus loves me! This I
know, For the Bible tells me so. Little ones to Him belong; They are weak, but
He is strong.

Refrain

Yes, Jesus loves me! Yes, Jesus loves me! Yes, Jesus loves me! The Bible tells
me so.

Jesus loves me! This I know, As He loved so long ago, Taking children on His
knee, Saying, “Let them come to Me.”


Refrain

Jesus loves me still today, Walking with me on my way, Wanting as a friend to
give Light and love to all who live.

Refrain

Jesus loves me! He who died Heaven’s gate to open wide; He will wash away my
sin, Let His little child come in.

Refrain

Jesus loves me! He will stay Close beside me all the way; Thou hast bled and
died for me, I will henceforth live for Thee.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All Things Bright And Beautiful</title> <content>All things bright
and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise and wonderful, The
Lord God made them all.

Each little flower that opens, Each little bird that sings, He made their
glowing colours, He made their tiny wings.

All things bright and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise
and wonderful, The Lord God made them all

The purple-headed mountain, The river running by, The sunset and the morning,
That brightens up the sky;

All things bright and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise
and wonderful, The Lord God made them all

The cold wind in the winter, The pleasant summer sun, The ripe fruits in the
garden, He made them every one;

All things bright and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise
and wonderful, The Lord God made them all

The tall trees in the greenwood, The meadows for our play, The rushes by the
water, To gather every day;

All things bright and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise
and wonderful, The Lord God made them all

He gave us eyes to see them, And lips that we might tell How great is God
Almighty, Who has made all things well.

All things bright and beautiful, All creatures great and small, All things wise
and wonderful, The Lord God made them all.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>All Creatures Of Our God And King</title> <content>All creatures
of our God and King Lift up your voice and with us sing, Alleluia! Alleluia!
Thou burning sun with golden beam, Thou silver moon with softer gleam!

Refrain

O praise Him! O praise Him! Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!

Thou rushing wind that art so strong Ye clouds that sail in Heaven along, O
praise Him! Alleluia! Thou rising moon, in praise rejoice, Ye lights of evening,
find a voice!

Refrain

Thou flowing water, pure and clear, Make music for thy Lord to hear, O praise
Him! Alleluia! Thou fire so masterful and bright, That givest man both warmth
and light.

Refrain

Dear mother earth, who day by day Unfoldest blessings on our way, O praise Him!
Alleluia! The flowers and fruits that in thee grow, Let them His glory also
show.

Refrain

And all ye men of tender heart, Forgiving others, take your part, O sing ye!
Alleluia! Ye who long pain and sorrow bear, Praise God and on Him cast your
care!

Refrain

And thou most kind and gentle Death, Waiting to hush our latest breath, O praise
Him! Alleluia! Thou leadest home the child of God, And Christ our Lord the way
hath trod.

Refrain

Let all things their Creator bless, And worship Him in humbleness, O praise Him!
Alleluia! Praise, praise the Father, praise the Son, And praise the Spirit,
Three in One!

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Lift High The Cross</title> <content>Refrain

Lift high the cross, the love of Christ proclaim, Till all the world adore His
sacred Name.

Led on their way by this triumphant sign, The hosts of God in conquering ranks
combine.

Refrain

Each newborn servant of the Crucified Bears on the brow the seal of Him Who
died.

Refrain

O Lord, once lifted on the glorious tree, As Thou hast promised, draw the world
to Thee.

Refrain

So shall our song of triumph ever be: Praise to the Crucified for victory.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>God Of Our Fathers</title> <content>God of our fathers, Whose
almighty hand Leads forth in beauty all the starry band Of shining worlds in
splendor through the skies Our grateful songs before Thy throne arise.

Thy love divine hath led us in the past, In this free land by Thee our lot is
cast, Be Thou our Ruler, Guardian, Guide and Stay, Thy Word our law, Thy paths
our chosen way.

From war’s alarms, from deadly pestilence, Be Thy strong arm our ever sure
defense; Thy true religion in our hearts increase, Thy bounteous goodness
nourish us in peace.

Refresh Thy people on their toilsome way, Lead us from night to never ending
day; Fill all our lives with love and grace divine, And glory, laud, and praise
be ever Thine.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I Come To The Garden Alone</title> <content>I come to the garden
alone While the dew is still on the roses And the voice I hear falling on my ear
The Son of God discloses.

Refrain

And He walks with me, and He talks with me, And He tells me I am His own; And
the joy we share as we tarry there, None other has ever known.

He speaks, and the sound of His voice, Is so sweet the birds hush their singing,
And the melody that He gave to me Within my heart is ringing.

Refrain

I’d stay in the garden with Him Though the night around me be falling, But He
bids me go; through the voice of woe His voice to me is calling.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Be Still My Soul </title> <content>Be still, my soul: the Lord is
on thy side. Bear patiently the cross of grief or pain. Leave to thy God to
order and provide; In every change, He faithful will remain. Be still, my soul:
thy best, thy heavenly Friend Through thorny ways leads to a joyful end.

Be still, my soul: thy God doth undertake To guide the future, as He has the
past. Thy hope, thy confidence let nothing shake; All now mysterious shall be
bright at last. Be still, my soul: the waves and winds still know His voice Who
ruled them while He dwelt below.

Be still, my soul: when dearest friends depart, And all is darkened in the vale
of tears, Then shalt thou better know His love, His heart, Who comes to soothe
thy sorrow and thy fears. Be still, my soul: thy Jesus can repay From His own
fullness all He takes away.

Be still, my soul: the hour is hastening on When we shall be forever with the
Lord. When disappointment, grief and fear are gone, Sorrow forgot, love’s purest
joys restored. Be still, my soul: when change and tears are past All safe and
blessèd we shall meet at last.

Be still, my soul: begin the song of praise On earth, be leaving, to Thy Lord on
high; Acknowledge Him in all thy words and ways, So shall He view thee with a
well pleased eye. Be still, my soul: the Sun of life divine Through passing
clouds shall but more brightly shine.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>I Vow To Thee My Country</title> <content>I vow to thee, my
country, all earthly things above, Entire and whole and perfect, the service of
my love: The love that asks no question, the love that stands the test, That
lays upon the altar the dearest and the best; The love that never falters, the
love that pays the price, The love that makes undaunted the final sacrifice.

And there's another country, I've heard of long ago, Most dear to them that love
her, most great to them that know; We may not count her armies, we may not see
her King; Her fortress is a faithful heart, her pride is suffering; And soul by
soul and silently her shining bounds increase, And her ways are ways of
gentleness and all her paths are peace.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Eternal Father Strong To Save </title> <content>Eternal Father,
strong to save, Whose arm hath bound the restless wave, Who biddest the mighty
ocean deep Its own appointed limits keep; Oh, hear us when we cry to Thee, For
those in peril on the sea!

O Christ! Whose voice the waters heard And hushed their raging at Thy Word, Who
walked on the foaming deep, And calm amidst its rage didst sleep; Oh, hear us
when we cry to Thee, For those in peril on the sea!

Most Holy Spirit! Who didst brood Upon the chaos dark and rude, And bid its
angry tumult cease, And give, for wild confusion, peace; Oh, hear us when we cry
to Thee, For those in peril on the sea!

O Trinity of love and power! Our family shield in danger’s hour; From rock and
tempest, fire and foe, Protect us wheresoever we go; Thus evermore shall rise to
Thee Glad hymns of praise from land and sea.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>He Who Would Valiant Be</title> <content>He who would valiant be
’gainst all disaster, Let him in constancy follow the Master. There’s no
discouragement shall make him once relent His first avowed intent to be a
pilgrim.

Who so beset him round with dismal stories Do but themselves confound - his
strength the more is. No foes shall stay his might; though he with giants fight,
He will make good his right to be a pilgrim.

Since, Lord, Thou dost defend us with Thy Spirit, We know we at the end, shall
life inherit. Then fancies flee away! I’ll fear not what men say, I’ll labor
night and day to be a pilgrim.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Onward Christian Soldiers</title> <content>Onward, Christian
soldiers, marching as to war, With the cross of Jesus going on before. Christ,
the royal Master, leads against the foe; Forward into battle see His banners go!

Refrain

Onward, Christian soldiers, marching as to war, With the cross of Jesus going on
before.

At the sign of triumph Satan’s host doth flee; On then, Christian soldiers, on
to victory! Hell’s foundations quiver at the shout of praise; Brothers lift your
voices, loud your anthems raise.

Refrain

Like a mighty army moves the church of God; Brothers, we are treading where the
saints have trod. We are not divided, all one body we, One in hope and doctrine,
one in charity.

Refrain

What the saints established that I hold for true. What the saints believèd, that
I believe too. Long as earth endureth, men the faith will hold, Kingdoms,
nations, empires, in destruction rolled.

Refrain

Crowns and thrones may perish, kingdoms rise and wane, But the church of Jesus
constant will remain. Gates of hell can never gainst that church prevail; We
have Christ’s own promise, and that cannot fail.

Refrain

Onward then, ye people, join our happy throng, Blend with ours your voices in
the triumph song. Glory, laud and honor unto Christ the King, This through
countless ages men and angels sing.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>We Plough The Fields And Scatter</title> <content>We plough the
fields and scatter The good seed on the land, But it is fed and watered By God's
almighty hand: He sends the snow in winter, The warmth to swell the grain, The
breezes and the sunshine, And soft, refreshing rain.

Refrain: All good gifts around us Are sent from heaven above; Then thank the
Lord, O thank the Lord, For all his love.

He only is the maker Of all things near and far; He paints the wayside flower,
He lights the evening star; The winds and waves obey him, By him the birds are
fed; Much more to us, his children, He gives our daily bread.

We thank thee then, O Father, For all things bright and good, The seed time and
the harvest, Our life, our health, our food. Accept the gifts we offer For all
thy love imparts, And what thou most desirest, Our humble, thankful hearts.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Shine On</title> <content>See the brightly shining star, As its
radiance beams afar, Guide the feet of weary pilgrims To the place where Jesus
lay. Like a beacon from its height, Burning brightly in the night, As the wise
men followed onward, Safely guided all the way. Refrain

Shine on! shine on! Beautiful star of light; Shine on! shine on! Cheering the
gloomy night; Shine on! shine on! Sending thy rays afar, Shine on thro’ the
darkness, Oh, thou fairest star.

It is shining still for thee, With a glory fair to see, As it leadeth ever
upward To the palace of the King. So we follow thro’ the night, Safely guided by
its light, While our hearts respond with gladness To the song the angels sing.

Refrain

So today that star alone Is the light to lead us on To the feet of Christ our
Savior, He our Prophet, Priest and King, As it brightly burns above, Sentry of
the King of love, While we follow onward, upward And His praises sweetly sing.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Secret Prayer</title> <content>Sweet secret prayer, comfort
divine, There, O my Lord, I know Thou art mine; Great Master, there in secret
with Thee, Heaven comes nearer and nearer to me. Refrain

Blessings attend and follow us there; Heaven comes nearer and nearer in prayer.

Sweet secret prayer, comfort divine, There do Thine arms, Lord, round me
entwine; Rivers of love and mercy there flow, Balm for all sorrow that mortal
can know.

Refrain

Sweet secret prayer, comfort divine, There do I feel I truly am Thine; Heav’n’s
windows open, Jesus is near, Near to my soul, and the Father will hear.

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Saved By the Blood</title> <content>Saved by the blood of the
Crucified One! Now ransomed from sin and a new work begun, Sing praise to the
Father and praise to the Son, Saved by the blood of the Crucified One! Refrain

Glory, I’m saved! Glory, I’m saved! My sins are all pardoned, my guilt is all
gone! Glory, I’m saved! Glory, I’m saved! I am saved by the blood of the
Crucified One!

Refrain

Saved by the blood of the Crucified One! The angels rejoicing because it is
done; A child of the Father, joint heir with the Son, Saved by the blood of the
Crucified One!

Refrain

Saved by the blood of the Crucified One! The Father He spake, and His will it
was done; Great price of my pardon, His own precious Son; Saved by the blood of
the Crucified One!

Refrain

Saved by the blood of the Crucified One! All hail to the Father, all hail to the
Son, All hail to the Spirit, the great Three in One! Saved by the blood of the
Crucified One!

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Sanctuary</title> <content>Lord, prepare me to be a sanctuary Pure
and holy, tried and true With thanksgiving, I'll be a living Sanctuary for You


Verse 2: It is you, Lord Who came to save The heart and soul of every man. It is
you Lord Who knows my weakness, Who gives me strength, With thine own hand.


Verse 3: Lead Me on Lord From temptation, Purify me From within. Fill my heart
with Your holy spirit, Take away All my sin.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Sail On!</title> <content>Upon a wide and stormy sea, Thou’rt
sailing to eternity, And thy great Admiral orders thee: “Sail on! Sail on! Sail
on!” Refrain

Sail on! Sail on! The storms will soon be past, The darkness will not always
last; Sail on! Sail on! God lives and He commands: “Sail on! Sail on!”

Art far from shore, and weary worn, The sky o’ercast, thy canvas torn? Hark ye!
a voice to thee is borne: “Sail on! Sail on! Sail on!”

Refrain

Do comrades tremble and refuse To further dare the taunting hues? No other
course is thine to choose, “Sail on! Sail on! Sail on!”

Refrain

Do snarling waves thy craft assail? Art pow’rless, drifting with the gale? Take
heart! God’s Word shall never fail. “Sail on! Sail on! Sail on!”

Refrain</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Safe Am I</title> <content>Safe am I, Safe am I, In the hollow of
His hand; Sheltered o'er, sheltered o'er With His love forever more No ill can
harm me, No foe alarm me, Fro He keeps both day and night, Safe am I, Safe am I,
In the hollow of His hand. </content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>Sabbath Day</title> <content>Sabbath day of rest and cheer! Day
divine, to me so dear! Come, O come to old and young, Gath’ring all for prayer
and song. Now the week of toil is o’er, And in peace we sit once more At our
Father’s ample board, Listening to His gracious Word.

Lord, our God, we seek Thy face, Bless us with Thy saving grace; May Thy heralds
everywhere Clear Thy Gospel truth declare.

Let Thy mighty Word hold sway Over men on earth today; Our poor souls, good
Shepherd, feed, Into pastures green us lead.

May, O Lord, the day be near, When we pass from trials here Into Thine eternal
rest, In the mansions of the blest.</content> </hymn>

<hymn> <title>A Sinner Forgiven</title> <content>To the hall of the feast came
the sinful and fair; She heard in the city that Jesus was there; Unheeding the
splendor that blazed on the board, She silently knelt at the feet of the Lord,
She silently knelt at the feet of the Lord. The frown and the murmur went round
thro’ them all, That one so unhallowed should tread in that hall; And some said
the poor would be objects more meet, As the wealth of her perfume she shower’d
on His feet, As the wealth of her perfume she shower’d on His feet.

She heard but the Savior; she spoke but with sighs; She dared not look up to the
heaven of His eyes; And hot tears gushed forth at each heave of her breast, As
her lips to His sandals were throbbingly pressed; As her lips to His sandals
were throbbingly pressed.

In the sky, after tempest, as shineth the bow, In glance of the sunshine, as
melteth the snow, He looked on that lost one: “her sins were forgiv’n,” And the
sinner went forth in the beauty of Heav’n; And the sinner went forth in the
beauty of Heav’n.</content> </hymn>

</hymns>

